<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Blue Book News</title>
		<link>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos</link>
		<description>Blue Book Online Services News provides up-to-date information on the top stories affecting you in the produce industry in the topic areas of bankruptcies, mergers, acquisitions, quarterly company results, PACA actions and more.</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>Copyright 2019 Blue Book Services</copyright>
		<image>
			<title>Blue Book Services News</title>
			 <url>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/en-us/images/logo-BBS-narrow.png</url>
			<link>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos\News.aspx</link>
		</image>
		<item>
	<title>Testing Bold in Posts</title>
	<description>ROCHESTER, N.Y.,&#160;April 29, 2019/PRNewswire/ --&#160;Wegmans &lt;a href=&#39;https://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/CompanyDetailsSummary.aspx?RL=CM&amp;CompanyID=104173&#39; target=&#39;_blank&#39;&gt;BB #:104173&lt;/a&gt; today announced that it&#39;s teaming up with the largest and fastest growing, last-mile logistics platform,&#160;&lt;u&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;amp;l=en&amp;amp;o=2449764-1&amp;amp;h=593115387&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.doordash.com%2F&amp;amp;a=DoorDash&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopener&quot;&gt;DoorDash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;, for delivery of the supermarket&#39;s popular restaurant-quality meals available in the new Wegmans Meals 2GO app. The venture is now live at the&#160;&lt;strong&gt;Dulles&#160;(Sterling)&lt;/strong&gt;&#160;store in northern&#160;Virginia, and the&#160;&lt;strong&gt;Pittsford,&#160;East Ave., and&#160;Perinton stores in&#160;Rochester, NY&lt;/strong&gt;.&#160;Two more&#160;Rochester-area stores,&#160;&lt;strong&gt;Penfield. and Holt Road&lt;/strong&gt;, are set to go live on&#160;April 30.&#160;&lt;u&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;amp;l=en&amp;amp;o=2449764-1&amp;amp;h=794829252&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.wegmans.com%2Fwegmans2go&amp;amp;a=Wegmans+Meals+2GO&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopener&quot;&gt;Wegmans Meals 2GO&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&#160;will roll out to more than 40 stores by year&#39;s end, with more to follow in 2020.</description>
	<pubDate>03 May 2019 10:00:32 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8437</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Rio Grande Valley sees inventive independent retailers</title>
	<description>While H-E-B and Walmart rule the roost throughout the Valley’s high-population areas, a handful of grocers have managed to find their niche in more remote, rural areas.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Mar 2019 07:00:01 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8220</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>What is Walmart doing with small format stores?</title>
	<description>A few stories have come across my news feed over the past few days suggesting Walmart (&lt;a href=&quot;https://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/CompanyDetailsSummary.aspx?RL=CM&amp;amp;CompanyID=143789&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;BB #:143789&lt;/a&gt;)&#160;is “quietly” closing stores in the next month or so.</description>
	<pubDate>26 Mar 2019 08:36:31 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8296</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>California HLB fight bolstered by Swiss fragrance company</title>
	<description>California stands alone among growing regions battling – and so far, containing – huanglongbing, and the latest investment shows that allies come from all over.</description>
	<pubDate>26 Mar 2019 04:45:02 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8284</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>E-commerce: the enemy of produce brands?</title>
	<description>I gave a talk last week in Tubac, AZ, to the Association of Table Grape Growers of Mexico at their annual Spring Summit. This was a repeat performance for me – I’ve previously addressed this group about grape merchandising trends in U.S. retailers.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Mar 2019 03:55:40 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8254</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>NGA pushes for more hunger relief at retail</title>
	<description>The National Grocers Association continues to work with USDA to allow NGA’s retail members better access to government food programs.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Mar 2019 03:50:53 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8250</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Management guru Morten Hansen to Keynote United Fresh</title>
	<description>WASHINGTON, D.C. (March 25, 2019) – Morten Hansen, one of the leading management authorities of our time, will set the stage for this year’s United Fresh Convention &amp;amp; Expo as keynote speaker during the United Fresh Breakfast General Session, Tuesday, June 11 at McCormick Place in Chicago.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Mar 2019 02:40:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8247</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>PMA Foodservice moves expo to Saturday, announces Keynote speakers</title>
	<description>&lt;em&gt;Newark, Del.&lt;/em&gt; - Two heavyweights in the food culture industry will share the marquee at Produce Marketing Association’s Foodservice Conference &amp;amp; Expo in Monterey, CA, in July.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Mar 2019 01:16:45 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8242</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>PBH launches food influencer network</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE March 25, 2019 – The Produce for Better Health Foundation (PBH) will launch its new elite influencer network – Fruit and Vegetable Ambassadors in Action (FVAA) – at the upcoming Consumer Connection Conference this April 22-25, 2019 in Scottsdale, AZ.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Mar 2019 12:48:18 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8238</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Nogales produce cargo could get a faster trip across the border</title>
	<description>TUBAC, AZ—The nearly $3 billion in produce crossings at the Mariposa Port of Entry in Nogales could get a faster ride through the border checkpoint if plans for a new cargo lane move forward as quickly as Customs and Border Protection hope.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Mar 2019 08:10:03 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8234</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Avocados recalled on positive Listeria sample</title>
	<description>Henry Avocado Corporation is voluntarily recalling California-grown whole avocados sold in bulk at retail stores because they have the potential to be contaminated with&#160;&lt;em&gt;Listeria monocytogenes&lt;/em&gt;. Henry Avocado is issuing this voluntary recall out of an abundance of caution due to positive test results on environmental samples taken during a routine government inspection at its California packing facility. There are no reported illnesses associated with this recall.</description>
	<pubDate>24 Mar 2019 08:19:17 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8230</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Kroger to sell Turkey Hill business</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE The Kroger Co.&#160;and Peak Rock Capital, a leading middle-market private equity firm based in &lt;span class=&quot;xn-location&quot;&gt;Austin, Texas&lt;/span&gt;, has announced a definitive agreement for the sale of Kroger&#39;s Turkey Hill business to an affiliate of Peak Rock Capital.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Mar 2019 09:28:42 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8193</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mexican grape estimate shows sharp increase over 2018</title>
	<description>TUBAC, AZ —The estimate is in earlier than usual this year, but if it holds, Mexican grape growers will export about 34% more boxes than in the 2018 season.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Mar 2019 07:46:19 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8184</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>When media swallows the Dirty Dozen</title>
	<description>It turns out mom was wrong, and I’m not supposed to eat my veggies because they’re toxic!</description>
	<pubDate>21 Mar 2019 01:47:13 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8172</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>&#39;Only Organic&#39; sums up the GRO Organic program</title>
	<description>As the organic sales growth rate slows, stakeholders embark on a new &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producebluebook.com/2019/03/05/organic-stakeholders-invest-1-5-million-to-advance-organic/&quot;&gt;voluntary check-off program&lt;/a&gt; of promotion, education and grower assistance.</description>
	<pubDate>21 Mar 2019 01:39:20 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8170</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Organic Produce Summit announces food waste session</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE With global food loss and waste estimated to be between one-third and one-half of all food produced, its impact on the environment and a company’s bottom line will be the subject of the third of six educational sessions at Organic Produce Summit 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>21 Mar 2019 10:30:53 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8168</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The New England Organic Produce Conference committee announces retailer roundtable participants</title>
	<description>The New England Produce Council (NEPC) and the Organic Produce Network (OPN) announced the retailer participants for the roundtable session.&#160; Brian Fleming (Stop &amp;amp; Shop Supermarket), Kevin Barry (Big Y Foods) and Mark Jewell (Hannaford Bros. Supermarket) will speak at the retailer roundtable on May 1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt; at the New England Organic Produce Conference being held at Gillette Stadium.</description>
	<pubDate>20 Mar 2019 03:39:46 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8165</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA cites Penny Tsigaris, d/b/a Manavi Produce, in New York for PACA violations</title>
	<description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) has cited &lt;strong&gt;Penny Tsigaris, doing business as Manavi Produce (Tsigaris dba Manavi), Oceanside, NY,&lt;/strong&gt; for failing to pay for produce.</description>
	<pubDate>20 Mar 2019 03:25:35 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8162</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Crecimiento de las exportaciones de aguacate: Per&#250;</title>
	<description>Se estima que se consumieron 8 millones de libras de guacamole en el die del Super Bowl el domingo de este a&#241;o, y la mayor&#237;a de ellas provino de M&#233;xico, ya que tiene un basti&#243;n en el mercado del aguacate en los Estados Unidos. Sin embargo, otro pa&#237;s latino est&#225; estableciendo nuevos r&#233;cords en la exportaci&#243;n de aguacate.</description>
	<pubDate>20 Mar 2019 11:56:05 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8158</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Avocado Export Growth: Peru</title>
	<description>&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producebluebook.com/2019/03/20/crecimiento-de-las-exportaciones-de-aguacate-peru/&quot;&gt;En espa&#241;ol&lt;/a&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>20 Mar 2019 11:49:47 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8156</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Studies contradict “Dirty Dozen” unsafe implication</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE Since 1995, an activist group has released a so-called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producebluebook.com/2019/03/20/dirty-dozen-clean-fifteen-lists-released/&quot;&gt;“dirty dozen” produce list&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
	<pubDate>20 Mar 2019 09:52:14 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8149</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Dirty Dozen, Clean Fifteen lists released</title>
	<description>Saying nearly 70 percent of fresh fruits and vegetables sold in the U.S. contain pesticide residue, the Environmental Working Group released its annual &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.ewg.org/foodnews/summary.php&quot;&gt;Shopper’s Guide to Pesticides in Produce&lt;/a&gt;, which includes its Dirty Dozen.</description>
	<pubDate>20 Mar 2019 09:43:37 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8146</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Walmart drops the ball with Savings Catcher cancellation</title>
	<description>&amp;nbsp;</description>
	<pubDate>19 Mar 2019 03:35:48 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8141</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA to raise inspection fees this fall</title>
	<description>USDA’s Specialty Crop Program inspections will rise Oct. 1, as it modernizes into a more data-driven, customer-focused organization.</description>
	<pubDate>19 Mar 2019 03:01:20 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8133</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Performance Food Group Company to acquire Eby-Brown Company LLC</title>
	<description>Performance Food Group Company has announced that it has signed a definitive agreement to acquire Eby-Brown Company LLC, a leading U.S. distributor of pre-packaged candy, snacks, specialty beverages and tobacco products in the convenience industry.</description>
	<pubDate>19 Mar 2019 02:50:59 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8131</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fresh Farms merges with Visalia Produce</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE The Molina Family of Hermosillo, Sonora, Mexico, is very excited to announce the merger of their two U.S. sales and distribution companies.</description>
	<pubDate>19 Mar 2019 02:37:21 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8128</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA lifts PACA reparation sanctions on New York produce business</title>
	<description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) announced that &lt;strong&gt;Utopia Produce, Inc.&lt;/strong&gt; satisfied a reparation order issued under the Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act (PACA).</description>
	<pubDate>19 Mar 2019 10:39:22 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8121</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA lifts PACA reparation sanctions on New York produce business</title>
	<description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) announced that &lt;strong&gt;Utopia Produce, Inc.&lt;/strong&gt; satisfied a reparation order issued under the Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act (PACA).</description>
	<pubDate>19 Mar 2019 10:39:22 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8121</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA lifts PACA reparation sanctions on California produce business</title>
	<description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) announced that &lt;strong&gt;Moceri Food &amp;amp; Beverage, Inc.&lt;/strong&gt; satisfied a reparation order issued under the Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act (PACA).</description>
	<pubDate>19 Mar 2019 10:27:54 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8119</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Expect higher prices for a smaller Vidalia onion crop</title>
	<description>Buyers should see a smaller crop of Vidalia onions this season, as the official first pack date has been set, and the overall onion market sees a spring price surge.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Mar 2019 03:57:31 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8112</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SXSW: The future of eating isn’t what you think</title>
	<description>AUSTIN, TX—With conference topics like dystopian future bug diets, customized nutrition and electronic baristas, a panel put together to discuss the future of eating at South by Southwest had a message many in the room didn’t expect.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Mar 2019 01:57:25 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8109</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Fresh releases 25 Retail Produce Manager Award Honorees</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE Marking 15 years of recognizing exceptional retail produce managers, on March 18 United Fresh Produce Association announced the honorees of its 2019 Retail Produce Manager Awards Program. The group of 25 produce managers represents supermarket banners, commissaries and independent retail stores from 16 different states and two Canadian provinces. The winners will be honored guests at the United Fresh 2019 convention, June 10-12 in Chicago.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Mar 2019 11:22:52 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8106</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Industry seeks changes to Hours of Service, Electronic Logging Device rules</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.unitedfresh.org/content/uploads/2019/03/HOS-Petition-for-perishable-commodities-3-15-19.pdf?utm_source=hs_email&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_content=70835468&amp;amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz--5YPCsnMInW_w8sPiXWHckpNcjfhXwLAVpL_szg1fC3KpNN8QASSL8Rwn7CL0dglDx-k7rnQ0qEbvEc_khGGBckQQZ9nSrPGgFLLuWyPlJNPdhddk&amp;amp;_hsmi=70835468&quot;&gt;petition for rulemaking&lt;/a&gt; was filed March 15 by United Fresh and other agricultural associations to receive modification to the Hours of Service (HOS) and Electronic Logging Device (ELD) rules for perishable fruit and vegetable commodities.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Mar 2019 09:55:51 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8103</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Grow. Don’t take the status quo</title>
	<description>There is no status quo associated with this dynamic industry. It is constantly changing.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Mar 2019 07:00:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8096</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Produce for Better Health Foundation releases line-up for Consumer Connection conference</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE March 15, 2019 – Produce for Better Health Foundation (PBH), a nonprofit organization whose mission is to improve Americans’ health and happiness by eating more fruits and vegetables every day, has confirmed an outstanding line-up for its 2019 Consumer Connection program.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Mar 2019 02:51:39 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8098</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Plenty of California navels at midseason</title>
	<description>California citrus growers are about halfway through harvesting a large crop with a wide size range.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Mar 2019 11:42:16 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8094</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Weis Markets reports results for 2018 and fourth quarter</title>
	<description>Weis Markets, Inc., has&#160;reported record total sales of over $3.5 billion for the 52-week period ended December 29, 2018, up 1.2 percent compared to the same period a year ago, while annual comparable store sales increased 0.7 percent.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Mar 2019 10:58:12 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8091</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Produce Reporter Week in Review: March 15, 2019</title>
	<description>Greg and Pamela talk about what the fresh produce industry can take away from visits to Southern Exposure and South by Southwest.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Mar 2019 08:49:41 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8087</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Dollar General paving way for fresh produce self-distribution</title>
	<description>Goodlettsville, TN-based Dollar General’s expansion into fresh food is prompting the company to accelerate its self-distribution with a new DG Fresh initiative.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Mar 2019 08:40:39 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8084</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Cheeselandia at SXSW...what fresh produce marketers can learn from 150 samples of cheese</title>
	<description>AUSTIN, TX -- The annual South by Southwest conference is well known for over-the-top promotions designed to generate buzz among attendees.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Mar 2019 12:06:41 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8078</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>MAP: Where in Houston can you get Kroger&#39;s driverless delivery?</title>
	<description>HOUSTON, March 14, 2019 /PRNewswire/ --&#160;The Kroger Co&lt;span id=&quot;spanHghlt7991&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&#160;(NYSE: KR), America&#39;s largest grocery retailer and Nuro, the robotics&#160;company transforming local commerce, today announced the launch of their autonomous grocery delivery service in Houston. The innovative service will be available through two Houston Kroger stores,&#160;reaching customers residing in four local zip codes.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Mar 2019 09:58:37 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8075</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Covenant Transportation Group announced fourth quarter 2018 financial and operating results</title>
	<description>Covenant Transportation Group, Inc.,&#160;announced&#160;financial and operating results for the fourth quarter ended December 31, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Mar 2019 04:42:02 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8070</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Limoneira Company announces first quarter fiscal year 2019 financial results</title>
	<description>Limoneira Company, a diversified citrus packing, selling, and marketing company with related agribusiness activities and real estate development operations, has reported financial results for the first quarter ended January 31, 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Mar 2019 04:34:48 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8067</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Roadrunner Transportation Systems reports fourth quarter and full year 2018 operating results</title>
	<description>Roadrunner Transportation Systems, Inc.,&#160;a leading asset-right transportation and asset-light logistics service provider, has announced results for the fourth quarter and year ended December 31, 2018 and the filing of its Annual Report on Form 10-K.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Mar 2019 04:26:17 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8064</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Fresh to present five Council Awards</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE WASHINGTON, D.C. (March 14, 2019) – New this year, United Fresh will honor five individuals for their outstanding work in sharing their expertise in different areas serving our produce industry. The honorees will be recognized at the United Fresh Convention &amp;amp; Expo June 10-12 in Chicago.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Mar 2019 03:51:14 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8061</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Apple growers visit Washington to talk trade, ag labor</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE Washington, D.C. (March 13, 2019)—More than 90 apple growers from across the nation met March 13 in Washington, D.C., to take part in the U.S. Apple Association’s (USApple) annual Capitol Hill Day. Meeting with more than 100 legislative offices during the fly-in, they expressed their support and concerns for priority issues like ratification of the U.S.-Mexico-Canada (USMCA) trade agreement, agriculture labor and implementation of the farm bill.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Mar 2019 03:45:43 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8059</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fresh produce needs even more SXSW representation</title>
	<description>AUSTIN, TX—As someone who has lived in the Austin area full time for nearly two decades, I’ve treated the annual South by Southwest conference with a local’s disdain and avoidance.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Mar 2019 08:31:07 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8028</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Produce with Pamela at SXSW</title>
	<description>AUSTIN, TX -- What is South by Southwest, and why is produce at the event? Cathy Burns from the Produce Marketing Association stopped by to chat at the PMA Global Street Farm.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Mar 2019 08:27:43 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8026</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Jim Lemke, president of Robinson Fresh, retires from C.H. Robinson</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE After nearly three decades of leadership, Jim Lemke, president of Robinson Fresh, a division of C.H. Robinson, announces plans to retire in 2019. Lemke will focus his remaining time at Robinson Fresh on ensuring a smooth leadership transition.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Mar 2019 02:30:51 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8023</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Pushing deeper in the snack market</title>
	<description>ORLANDO, FL – Produce marketers have been advised to offer their products in more places for more consumer eating opportunities, and it was clear on the expo floor of Southern Exposure, March 9, they’re putting that advice into practice.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Mar 2019 12:00:15 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8010</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mastronardi Produce and John Paul DeJoria announce partnership to revolutionize fresh food availability</title>
	<description>Mastronardi Produce&#174;, the leading greenhouse company in North America, announced today that it has teamed up with John Paul DeJoria to make quality, flavorful produce more widely accessible. The partnership will focus on developing Advanced High-Density Farming Systems to grow local fresh food in underserved markets around the globe.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Mar 2019 11:46:06 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8008</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA cites Paradise Produce LLC in Nevada for PACA violations</title>
	<description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) has cited Paradise Produce LLC, Las Vegas, Nev., for failure to pay for produce.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Mar 2019 11:33:53 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=8003</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SXSW: Health alone won’t increase consumption</title>
	<description>AUSTIN, TX—It’s no secret that fresh produce checks all the boxes for health and wellness, but the problem is people’s food decisions – for the most part – aren’t rational.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Mar 2019 08:15:53 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7983</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Iceberg lettuce – not so ordinary</title>
	<description>Iceberg or head lettuce is not typically thought of as exceptional.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Mar 2019 03:09:43 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7965</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Organic Cuties debut at SEPC</title>
	<description>ORLANDO, FL – Sun Pacific Marketing Cooperative, Pasadena, CA, showed its organic Cuties for the first time at the Southeast Produce Council’s Southern Exposure expo March 9.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Mar 2019 02:59:05 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7958</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Wholesum to expand Fair Trade reach with organic artichokes program</title>
	<description>Wholesum™ announced today that they will be growing their Fair Trade certified program by introducing organically grown artichokes from Salinas, California with harvests starting at the end of April. The organic artichokes will be grown by a California based partner farm, who is committed to growing organically with Fair Trade certification.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Mar 2019 02:28:10 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7952</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>American employers harmed by decision to limit Mexican tomatoes</title>
	<description>Up to 33,000 American jobs are threatened by a Department of Commerce decision that would have the double impact of increasing tomato prices for American consumers.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Mar 2019 02:08:49 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7945</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Apeel gets retail validation from Midwest chain</title>
	<description>ORLANDO, FL – A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producebluebook.com/2019/03/08/apeel-science-helping-martins-to-virtually-eliminate-shrink-in-avocado-category/&quot;&gt;Midwest retail chain&lt;/a&gt; tested Apeel’s plant-based coatings on its avocados and liked it enough to commit fully to the technology.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Mar 2019 02:03:12 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7943</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Guatemalan Produce Trade Association continues growth</title>
	<description>The Guatemalan Produce Trade Association (GPTA), comprised of the major importers and key players in the Guatemalan produce trade, is amplifying its influence and involvement in strategic issues and industry events. Members of the association share their perspective and outlook for Guatemala’s continuing trade.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Mar 2019 09:06:26 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7937</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The food desert solution: fast, cheap…and fresh</title>
	<description>AUSTIN, TX—Food deserts don’t happen because people don’t want to eat healthy food.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Mar 2019 08:26:51 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7933</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SEPC: Translating science into action</title>
	<description>ORLANDO, FL – Some of the smartest people in the produce industry work in food safety, but if that work isn’t turned into something useable and explained to the rest of the industry, it won’t be as effective.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Mar 2019 01:49:56 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7890</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fullei Fresh recalls organic bean sprouts</title>
	<description>Fullei Fresh of Miami, Florida is voluntarily recalling Organic Bean Sprouts because it has the potential to be contaminated with Listeria monocytogenes, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Mar 2019 11:40:19 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7885</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SEPC: Retailers adjust to shifting consumer demand</title>
	<description>ORLANDO, FL – Now that “produce department” has overtaken “price” as the No.1 reason consumers choose a grocery store, retailers must find their best way to deliver a good experience.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Mar 2019 07:51:19 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7870</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Wegmans tops another list</title>
	<description>How can a company that operates in only six states rank so high in yet another nationwide list? In this case, Rochester, NY-based Wegmans Food Markets&#39; reputation precedes it.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Mar 2019 07:14:07 -0400</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7867</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Natural Foods, Inc. reports second quarter fiscal 2019 results</title>
	<description>United Natural Foods, Inc.,&#160;has reported financial results for the second quarter of fiscal 2019 ended January&#160;26, 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Mar 2019 04:31:03 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7864</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Calavo Growers, Inc. announces fiscal 2019 first quarter results</title>
	<description>Calavo Growers, Inc., has reported that fiscal 2019 first quarter adjusted net income rose 36 percent on a 17 percent increase in gross profit over the corresponding period last year. Operating income advanced 53 percent in the most-recent quarter, according to the company, a global avocado-industry leader and expanding provider of value-added fresh food.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Mar 2019 04:27:27 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7862</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Let&#39;s go to The Mango Store</title>
	<description>I’m kind of sad I didn’t get a chance to visit the “The Mango Store,” a “one-day opportunity to discover the culture, flavor, nutrition and versatility of mangos,” in New York on March 7.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Mar 2019 04:05:49 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7854</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SEPC: Exploring food as medicine</title>
	<description>ORLANDO, FL – For years fresh produce marketers have operated on the principle that consumers know fruits and vegetables are good for them, but they don’t eat as much as they should because of taste, convenience or price.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Mar 2019 12:41:13 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7829</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Apeel Science Helping Martin&#39;s to Virtually Eliminate Shrink in Avocado Category</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE Just a few weeks in, Apeel Avocados are soon to represent 100% of the fresh avocados offered at Martin’s Super Markets.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Mar 2019 10:00:39 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7940</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Kroger plans to expand self-driving grocery delivery pilot</title>
	<description>Kroger Co. CEO Rodney McMullen said the company has expanded Home Chef meal kits to an additional 500 markets, and other pilot programs are slated for expansion.</description>
	<pubDate>07 Mar 2019 09:08:28 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7817</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Costco posts Q2 sales growth but not in fresh</title>
	<description>Costco Wholesale Corp. showed a 7.3 percent sales increase in the second quarter but noted fresh food sales dropped a little.</description>
	<pubDate>07 Mar 2019 09:06:30 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7816</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Harmonized Standard Audit now available</title>
	<description>WASHINGTON, D.C. (March 7, 2019) – United Fresh is pleased to announce that the Harmonized Standard Audit is now available from the following auditing organizations:</description>
	<pubDate>07 Mar 2019 03:04:18 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7814</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>No, avocados are not pricier because of fad diets</title>
	<description>A recent Wall Street Journal article sent me down a rabbit hole of data. The article, published Feb 25, claimed “Your Avocados and Olives are Pricier Because Fat is in Fashion.”</description>
	<pubDate>07 Mar 2019 02:24:02 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7804</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>PMA taps out-of-this-world speaker for Fresh Connections: Mexico</title>
	<description>&lt;span style=&quot;color: black&quot;&gt; Former astronaut Jos&#233; Hern&#225;ndez is the featured speaker at Produce Marketing Association’s (PMA) Fresh Connections: Mexico scheduled May 29-30 at the Hotel Hard Rock in Guadalajara, Jalisco, Mexico.&#160;&lt;/span&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>07 Mar 2019 02:11:41 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7799</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Oppy chosen as Canada’s Best Managed for 18th year</title>
	<description>What makes a “best managed” company? According to the global financial services company Deloitte, companies with best-in-class business practices—like the Vancouver, BC-based Oppy—demonstrate exceptional strategy, capability, commitment, and return on investment.</description>
	<pubDate>07 Mar 2019 05:53:33 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7775</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>UNFI: Supervalu “disappointing,” Albert’s to integrate conventional produce</title>
	<description>United Natural Foods Inc. executives said even though they’ve been disappointed with the performance of Supervalu’s business since the acquisition this summer, they’d make the same decision again.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Mar 2019 08:57:23 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7779</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Carton advancements double avocado shelf life for WP Produce</title>
	<description>Avocado demand is up across the board, but tropical — or green skin — avocados have shelf life challenges that can be a barrier for expansion in some markets.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Mar 2019 11:49:30 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7771</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Pure Flavor’s new Georgia greenhouse growing results</title>
	<description>Now almost 3 months since their first picks of fresh greenhouse grown vegetables from their new Fort Valley, GA greenhouse facility, Pure Flavor&#174; has started to change the landscape in the southeast.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Mar 2019 08:40:43 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7766</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Stakeholders invest $1.5 million to advance organic</title>
	<description>Washington, D.C., March 05, 2019 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Much can happen in a year, as a major collective effort underway by the organic community is proving. Scores of organic companies and stakeholders have enthusiastically stepped up to invest almost $1.5 million in programs to advance organic food and farming -- initiatives to promote organic, educate consumers about organic’s benefits, assist organic farmers and foster critical organic research. And this is just the beginning.</description>
	<pubDate>05 Mar 2019 05:22:54 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7759</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>FDA commissioner Gottlieb to step down</title>
	<description>U.S. Food and Drug Administration commissioner Scott Gottlieb resigned today.</description>
	<pubDate>05 Mar 2019 05:18:04 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7757</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SpartanNash launches Kids Crew program for retail</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;GRAND RAPIDS, Mich.&lt;/strong&gt;&#160;– To encourage healthy eating choices for children and reinforce its commitment to health and wellness in every aisle of its retail stores, SpartanNash today introduced its new Kids Crew program.</description>
	<pubDate>05 Mar 2019 02:14:13 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7751</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Trader Joe’s reduces plastic in produce packaging</title>
	<description>Traditionally close-mouthed Trader Joe’s subtly announced in its latest Fearless Flyer newsletter it plans to start reducing plastic throughout its store, including fresh produce packaging.</description>
	<pubDate>05 Mar 2019 01:41:03 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7748</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Puerto de Virginia est&#225; listo para m&#225;s productos frescos sudamericanos</title>
	<description>El Departamento de Agricultura de los Estados Unidos ha otorgado al Puerto de Virginia la aprobaci&#243;n para importar fruta sudamericana esta semana.</description>
	<pubDate>05 Mar 2019 12:44:23 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7744</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Port of Virginia is ready for more South American produce</title>
	<description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture has given the Port of Virginia approval to import South American fruit this week.</description>
	<pubDate>05 Mar 2019 12:40:49 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7741</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Matson, Inc. announces fourth quarter and full year 2018 results</title>
	<description>Matson, Inc.,&#160;a leading U.S. carrier in the Pacific, has reported net income of $20.6 million, or $0.48 per diluted share, for the quarter ended December 31, 2018.&#160; Net income for the quarter ended December 31, 2017 was $166.9 million, or $3.90 per diluted share.&#160; Net income and earnings per share in the fourth quarter of 2017 benefitted by $155.0 million and $3.62 per diluted share, respectively, from a one-time, non-cash tax adjustment arising from the enactment of the Tax Cuts and Jobs Act of 2017 (the &quot;Tax Act&quot;).&#160; Consolidated revenue for the fourth quarter 2018 was $564.9 million compared with $516.1 million for the fourth quarter 2017.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Mar 2019 04:44:28 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7731</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Chefs’ Warehouse reports fourth quarter 2018 financial results</title>
	<description>The Chefs’ Warehouse, Inc.,&#160;a premier distributor of specialty food products in the United States and Canada, has reported financial results for its fourth quarter ended December&#160;28, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Mar 2019 04:36:37 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7729</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hub Group, Inc. reports record fourth quarter 2018 results</title>
	<description>Hub Group, Inc., has announced fourth quarter 2018 net income of $48.9 million, or diluted earnings per share of $1.46. Income from continuing operations for the current quarter was $33.7 million, or $1.01 per diluted share.&#160; Income from discontinued operations for the current quarter was $15.2 million, or $0.45 per diluted share.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Mar 2019 04:27:46 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7726</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Werner Enterprises reports fourth quarter and full year 2018 results</title>
	<description>Werner Enterprises, Inc., one of the nation’s largest transportation and logistics companies,&#160;has reported financial results for the fourth quarter and full year ended December 31, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Mar 2019 04:23:35 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7723</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Gelson&#39;s relaunches Chef&#39;d meal kits</title>
	<description>NEWPORT BEACH, Calif.,&#160;March 4, 2019&#160;/PRNewswire/ -- True Food Innovations, based in&#160;Newport Beach, California, is launching new products under both True Chef™&#160;and Chef&#39;d™ branded retail meal kits&#160;with fresh, clean label, preservative-free recipes in Gelson&#39;s Markets. All recipes only require 15 minutes of total prep and cook time.&lt;strong&gt;&#160;&#160;&lt;/strong&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>04 Mar 2019 03:58:08 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7718</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SEPC and 20 years of Southern Exposure</title>
	<description>The Southeast Produce Council has seen its Southern Exposure annual conference emerge as a must-see event as it celebrates its 20th anniversary this week.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Mar 2019 03:11:15 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7712</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Publix announces fourth quarter and annual results for 2018</title>
	<description>Publix’s sales for the three months ended Dec. 29, 2018 were $9.3 billion, a 3.8 percent increase from $8.9 billion in 2017. Comparable store sales for the three months ended Dec. 29, 2018 increased 1.1 percent.Net earnings for the three months ended Dec. 29, 2018 were $407 million, compared to $766.6 million in 2017, a decrease of 46.9 percent. Earnings per share for the three months ended Dec. 29, 2018 decreased to $0.57 per share, down from $1.04 per share in 2017.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 04:33:06 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7694</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USMCA delay has ag groups concerned</title>
	<description>Agriculture interests, including several in fresh produce, are pushing for adoption of the United States-Mexico-Canada Agreement, but the government shut down has caused its progress to slow.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 04:31:24 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7691</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USA Truck reports fourth quarter 2018 results</title>
	<description>USA Truck, Inc.,&#160;a leading capacity solutions provider, has announced its financial results for the three and twelve months ended December 31, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 04:18:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7687</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>B&amp;amp;G&#160;Foods reports financial results for fourth quarter and full year 2018</title>
	<description>B&amp;amp;G&#160;Foods,&#160;Inc.,&#160;has announced financial results for the fourth quarter and full year 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 04:11:03 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7684</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Blue Apron&#160;Holdings, Inc.&#160;reports fourth quarter and full-year 2018 results</title>
	<description>Blue Apron Holdings, Inc.&#160;has announced financial results for the quarter and full year ended December 31, 2018. Blue Apron also announced today the transfer of production volume from its Arlington facility to its Linden facility with additional information available in the company’s Current Report on Form 8-K. Blue Apron will hold its scheduled earnings call and webcast tomorrow, January 31, at 8:30 a.m. Eastern Time to discuss its fourth quarter and full year 2018 results and business outlook.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 04:05:04 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7681</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Retail stocks gasp at Amazon grocery news</title>
	<description>At approximately 12:38 Eastern Standard Time, the world of grocery stocks took a deep breath…and dropped. Just minutes before, the Wall Street Journal broke a story saying Amazon’s launching a new grocery banner.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 04:01:51 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7678</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>C. H. Robinson reports 2018 fourth quarter and full-year results</title>
	<description>C.H. Robinson Worldwide, Inc., has reported financial results for the quarter and fiscal year ended December&#160;31, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 04:00:08 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7677</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Landstar System reports record fourth quarter&#160;revenue</title>
	<description>Landstar System, Inc.,&#160;has reported record fourth quarter revenue of $1.182 billion in the 2018 fourth quarter, a 12 percent increase over revenue of $1.052 billion reported in the 2017 fourth quarter. Gross profit (defined as revenue less the cost of purchased transportation and commissions to agents) in the 2018 fourth quarter was $168.9 million, 13 percent above the 2017 fourth quarter, while 2018 fourth quarter operating income was $86.1 million, 23 percent above the 2017 fourth quarter. Operating income and gross profit in the 2018 fourth quarter were also each fourth quarter records.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 03:20:08 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7674</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA files action against CKF Produce Corp. in New York for alleged PACA violations</title>
	<description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) has filed a Notice to Show Cause and complaint under the Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act (PACA) against CKF Produce Corp. (CKF).&#160; The company, operating from New York, allegedly failed to make payment to 22 produce sellers in the amount of $916,442 from March 2017 through November 2018.&#160; USDA asserts that CKF is unfit to be licensed under PACA due to the alleged violations.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 03:13:12 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7667</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Report: Amazon to launch new grocery brand</title>
	<description>Amazon plans to open grocery stores in several large U.S. cities, distinct from its Whole Foods brand.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 01:48:26 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7661</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Produce Reporter Week in Review: March 1, 2019</title>
	<description>Greg and Pamela talk about some of the top stories this week, including:</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 09:15:52 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7657</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Fresh announces nominations for new board officers and directors</title>
	<description>WASHINGTON, D.C. (March 1, 2019) – United Fresh Immediate Past Chair &lt;strong&gt;Susan Reimer-Sifford&lt;/strong&gt; Fresh Connect, LLC, has announced the slate of new officers and directors nominated to serve on the United Fresh Produce Association Board of Directors, effective at its March 25, 2019 meeting in Nashville, TN.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Mar 2019 09:09:31 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7655</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>FDA releases imported food safety guide</title>
	<description>The Food and Drug Administration released a statement from FDA Commissioner Scott Gottlieb, M.D., and Deputy Commissioner Frank Yiannas&#160;&lt;span style=&quot;float: none;background-color: transparent;color: #333333;cursor: text;font-family: Georgia,&#39;Times New Roman&#39;,&#39;Bitstream Charter&#39;,Times,serif;font-size: 16px;font-style: normal;font-variant: normal;font-weight: 400;letter-spacing: normal;text-align: left;text-decoration: none;text-indent: 0px&quot;&gt;February 25&lt;/span&gt; on a new strategy to advance FDA’s food safety mission and modernize oversight of imported food.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Feb 2019 02:31:29 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7619</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Study finds equal quality fresh foods at dollar stores</title>
	<description>As deep discount stores, so-called “dollar stores,” add more fresh food to their lineup, a new study by the University of Nevada, Las Vegas, found produce quality was virtually the same as traditional grocers in the area.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Feb 2019 12:01:59 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7611</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>PMA names new CGT Executive Director</title>
	<description>The Produce Marketing Association and Center for Growing Talent have named Doug Bohr as the charitable organization’s next Executive Director.&#160; Bohr will join Center for Growing Talent (CGT) March 20, 2019 as longtime leader, Margi Prueitt, retires after 9 years at the helm.&#160; Bohr will oversee leadership for CGT, help advance their fundraising efforts, and the continued work to provide solutions to attract, develop and retain the talent the produce and floral communities need to grow.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Feb 2019 10:52:44 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7608</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>NGA to independent grocers: You be you</title>
	<description>SAN DIEGO -- The overall feeling at the National Grocers Association annual convention was one of optimism for independent grocers in the face of increasing competition.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Feb 2019 10:44:15 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7604</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Viva Fresh Expo Announces 2019 Education Program</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Mission, Texas: February 27, 2019: &lt;/strong&gt;The 2019 Viva Fresh Produce Expo is excited to announce the agenda for this year’s educational sessions.&#160;&#160; The lineup will include a wide-range of topics from steps on how to prevent a food-safety crisis to practical applications of the “food as medicine” movement along with retail trends according to Google.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Feb 2019 10:03:59 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7599</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mexico Spring Grape Summit moves to Tubac, AZ</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE The Table Grape Growers Association in Mexico invites the industry to participate in the Mexico Spring Summit 2019, to be held in for the first time in Tubac, AZ, on Thursday, March 21st, 2019, at the Tubac Golf Resort &amp;amp; Spa, from 1:00 pm to 10:00 pm. Blue Book&#39;s Retail Editor Pamela Riemenschneider will be among the presenters, speaking about e-commerce. For registrations please visit: &lt;a href=&quot;http://summit.aalpum.org/&quot;&gt;www.summit.aalpum.org&lt;/a&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>27 Feb 2019 03:56:40 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7594</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Amanda Keefer of Produce for Kids talks the Mission for Nutrition</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Orlando, Fla. – Feb. 25 – &lt;/strong&gt;Produce for Kids&#174; is aligning with health-conscious brands, commodities and retail dietitians to kick off its inaugural Mission for Nutrition promotion in celebration of National Nutrition Month&#174;. The online and in-store program focuses on the importance of a healthy family diet and the value of meal planning and prepping while aiming to increase the consumption of fresh produce.</description>
	<pubDate>27 Feb 2019 03:39:22 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7591</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Merchantability – The Other Warranty</title>
	<description>The warranty of merchantability usually finds itself in the shadow of the warranty of suitable shipping condition (i.e., the warranty whereby sellers promise that their product will make good arrival).&#160; But the food safety outbreaks in 2018 brought a fair amount of attention to this lesser-known warranty.</description>
	<pubDate>27 Feb 2019 01:23:33 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7589</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>NGA: Grocery wholesalers spell out independents’ advantages</title>
	<description>SAN DIEGO – Even with all the changes the grocery industry deals with, when it comes to working with grocery wholesalers one challenge remains for independent retailers: retaining their niche.</description>
	<pubDate>27 Feb 2019 12:13:27 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7584</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Campbell and affiliate of Fountain of Health USA sign definitive agreement for sale of Garden Fresh Gourmet</title>
	<description>Campbell Soup Company announced that it has signed a definitive agreement for the sale of Garden Fresh Gourmet to an affiliate of Fountain of Health USA, a maker of hummus, dips, variety packs, prepared salads, p&#226;t&#233;s, and frozen desserts. Terms of the transaction were not disclosed.</description>
	<pubDate>27 Feb 2019 11:28:31 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7582</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA restricts PACA violators in Florida, Illinois, New York and Pennsylvania from Operating in the produce industry</title>
	<description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) has imposed sanctions on five produce businesses for failure to pay reparation awards issued under the Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act (PACA).</description>
	<pubDate>27 Feb 2019 09:38:02 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7572</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Mexican growers challenge Department of Commerce over Tomato Suspension Agreement</title>
	<description>&lt;span class=&quot;xn-location&quot;&gt;WASHINGTON&lt;/span&gt;,&#160;&lt;span class=&quot;xn-chron&quot;&gt;Feb. 25, 2019&lt;/span&gt;&#160;/PRNewswire/ --&#160;The Mexican tomato growers today filed a complaint with&#160;&lt;span class=&quot;xn-location&quot;&gt;the United States&lt;/span&gt;&#160;Court of International Trade challenging the U.S. Department of Commerce&#39;s determination in the 2018 sunset review of the agreement suspending the antidumping investigation on imports of fresh tomatoes from&#160;&lt;span class=&quot;xn-location&quot;&gt;Mexico&lt;/span&gt;.</description>
	<pubDate>27 Feb 2019 08:56:42 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7568</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>MAP: See which Shop ‘n Save stores will become Martin’s Food Markets</title>
	<description>Giant Food Stores LLC’s proposed purchase of Supervalu’s Shop ‘n Save stores has been given approval by the Federal Trade Commission.</description>
	<pubDate>26 Feb 2019 04:51:51 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7561</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Pasado, presente y futuro del Acuerdo de Suspensi&#243;n de Tomate</title>
	<description>&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producebluebook.com/2019/02/26/tomato-suspension-agreement-past-present-and-future/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Editor&#39;s Note: Click here to read this article in English.&#160;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>26 Feb 2019 02:55:34 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7544</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Tomato Suspension: What&#39;s next?</title>
	<description>&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producebluebook.com/2019/02/26/pasado-presente-y-futuro-del-acuerdo-de-suspension-de-tomate/&quot;&gt;En espa&#241;ol.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>26 Feb 2019 02:22:39 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7538</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Listeria find prompts value-added green bean, squash recall</title>
	<description>Southern Specialties Inc. of Pompano Beach, Florida is voluntarily recalling select bags of Marketside brand green beans and butternut squash because they have the potential to be contaminated with&#160;&lt;em&gt;Listeria monocytogenes&lt;/em&gt;, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea,&#160;&lt;em&gt;Listeria&lt;/em&gt;&#160;infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	<pubDate>26 Feb 2019 12:49:54 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7532</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Brambles sale of IFCO RPC pooling business for $2.51 billion</title>
	<description>Sydney – 25 February 2019: Brambles today announced that it has entered into a binding agreement to sell its IFCO reusable plastic containers (RPC) business to Triton and Luxinva (a wholly-owned subsidiary of the Abu Dhabi Investment Authority) for an enterprise value of US$2.51bn. The transaction is subject to customary regulatory approvals and is expected to be completed during the second quarter of calendar year 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>26 Feb 2019 11:49:41 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7528</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>NGA: Hy-Vee perishables manager wins Best Bagger</title>
	<description>SAN DIEGO – Dwayne Campbell, assistant manager of perishables for a Hy-Vee store in Des Moines, IA, is the winner of the 2019 Best Bagger contest held at the National Grocers Association Show on Feb. 25.</description>
	<pubDate>26 Feb 2019 08:11:40 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7521</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Stop &amp;amp; Shop union votes to strike, contract negotiations continue</title>
	<description>A Boston area chapter of the United Food and Commercial Workers has voted to strike after Quincy, MA-based Stop &amp;amp; Shop’s contract with employees expired.</description>
	<pubDate>26 Feb 2019 07:32:33 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7515</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>New tax options for produce companies</title>
	<description>Need I say it is tax season?</description>
	<pubDate>25 Feb 2019 07:26:43 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7510</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Fresh Releases Q4 2018 FreshFacts on Retail Report</title>
	<description>WASHINGTON, D.C. (February 25, 2019) – Fresh produce continues to play an important role in fourth quarter holiday sales, according to the United Fresh Produce Association’s Q4 2018 &amp;amp; 2018 Year in Review edition of the &lt;em&gt;FreshFacts&lt;sup&gt;&#174;&lt;/sup&gt; on Retail&lt;/em&gt; report.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Feb 2019 06:57:50 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7505</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>NGA: How to compete with dollar stores</title>
	<description>SAN DIEGO – Dollar stores present serious competition to independent retailers, increasingly in food, but there are a few key ways to differentiate with them.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Feb 2019 06:52:14 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7502</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>NGA: How to compete with deep discounters</title>
	<description>SAN DIEGO – Deep discount retailers’ growth is on the rise, and independent grocers need to focus on what they do better to keep from becoming victims of the discounters’ success.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Feb 2019 04:23:12 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7497</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Watch out for frozen foods</title>
	<description>“For the first time in years, the perimeter isn’t quite the slam dunk sales driver it has been.”</description>
	<pubDate>25 Feb 2019 08:01:40 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7493</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>NGA: How to compete with online retailers</title>
	<description>SAN DIEGO – Independent retailers can fight against the competition of online grocery by being more of what they already are online and in stores.</description>
	<pubDate>24 Feb 2019 09:57:11 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7490</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>MAP: See which Southeastern Grocers are closing</title>
	<description>Less than a year after closing nearly 100 underperforming stores amid bankruptcy restructuring, Jacksonville, FL-based Southeastern Grocers announced more store closures.</description>
	<pubDate>24 Feb 2019 09:38:56 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7486</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Stemilt pears no longer use anti-ripening agents</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE WENATCHEE, Wash. – Pear season is well underway and Stemilt Growers’ Operation Flavor program continues towards pear improvement with their most recent announcement: effective the 2018/19 crop year, Stemilt will no longer be using anti-ripening agents on any pear variety that comes through Stemilt’s doors. This bold industry unique move is aimed at the consumer.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Feb 2019 04:17:27 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7481</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Wilcox Fresh welcomes new CEO</title>
	<description>Floyd Wilcox &amp;amp; Sons Inc.&#160;(dba Wilcox Fresh) is excited to announce and welcome &lt;strong&gt;Justin Reynolds&lt;/strong&gt; as the company’s new CEO. Reynolds has been involved in Idaho agriculture for 15 years in everything from labor and production roles to financial services and management leadership positions.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Feb 2019 03:55:15 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7478</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Key buyers to attend PMA Fresh Connections: Retail</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE Newark, Del. – More than 30 produce buyers from 24 companies are scheduled to attend Produce Marketing Association’s (PMA) Fresh Connections: Retail event April 10-11 in Philadelphia, including first timers Coburn’s Inc., Gerrity’s Supermarkets, Longo’s Brothers Markets, Sprouts Farmers Market, The Stop &amp;amp; Shop Supermarket Co., and Whole Foods Market.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Feb 2019 02:29:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7470</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Key buyers to attend PMA Fresh Connections: Retail</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE Newark, Del. – More than 30 produce buyers from 24 companies are scheduled to attend Produce Marketing Association’s (PMA) Fresh Connections: Retail event April 10-11 in Philadelphia, including first timers Coburn’s Inc., Gerrity’s Supermarkets, Longo’s Brothers Markets, Sprouts Farmers Market, The Stop &amp;amp; Shop Supermarket Co., and Whole Foods Market.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Feb 2019 02:29:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7470</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Key buyers to attend PMA Fresh Connections: Retail</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE Newark, Del. – More than 30 produce buyers from 24 companies are scheduled to attend Produce Marketing Association’s (PMA) Fresh Connections: Retail event April 10-11 in Philadelphia, including first timers Coburn’s Inc., Gerrity’s Supermarkets, Longo’s Brothers Markets, Sprouts Farmers Market, The Stop &amp;amp; Shop Supermarket Co., and Whole Foods Market.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Feb 2019 02:29:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7470</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hormel Foods reports first quarter results &amp;amp; reaffirms fiscal 2019 guidance</title>
	<description>Hormel Foods Corporation, a leading global branded food company, has reported results for the first quarter of fiscal 2019. All comparisons are to the first quarter of fiscal 2018 unless otherwise noted.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Feb 2019 01:38:50 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7464</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fast-tracking fresh for mid-market retailers: iTradeNetwork introduces a new fresh trading, traceability and supply chain analytics platform</title>
	<description>iTradeNetwork, the leading global provider of on-demand supply chain management and intelligence solutions for the food and beverage industry, is proud to announce a new fresh trading, traceability, inspection, and analytics platform specially tailored to ambitious mid-market retailers.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Feb 2019 01:36:45 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7463</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Campbell and Joshua Green Corporation sign definitive agreement for sale of Campbell Fresh plant</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Campbell Soup Company&#160;&lt;/strong&gt;has announced&#160;that it has signed a definitive agreement for the sale of its Everett, Washington, refrigerated soup plant to an affiliate of the Joshua Green Corporation (JGC), a Seattle-based private investment company. Terms of the transaction were not disclosed.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Feb 2019 01:12:42 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7460</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Seaboard Corporation reported earnings for period ended December 31, 2018</title>
	<description>Seaboard Corporation, Merriam, Kansas, has now reported earnings for the three and twelve months ended December&#160;31,&#160;2018, and December&#160;31,&#160;2017, in millions of dollars except share and per share amounts.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Feb 2019 08:47:00 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7451</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Produce Reporter Week in Review: February 22, 2019</title>
	<description>Greg visits with Pamela, who is covering the annual &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producebluebook.com/2019/02/22/united-freshs-brandstorm-boasts-record-attendance-again/&quot;&gt;Brandstorm marketing conference&lt;/a&gt; in San Francisco, about the meeting and some news on limes and avocados.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Feb 2019 08:24:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7446</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Fresh’s Brandstorm boasts record attendance -- again</title>
	<description>SAN FRANCISCO—While many areas of the country are suffering storms they’d rather not see this time of year, the United Fresh Produce Association’s fourth annual Brandstorm marketing conference is celebrating record attendance.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Feb 2019 08:09:52 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7443</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Sprouts reports continued sales growth in Q4</title>
	<description>Sprouts Farmers Market reported a successful fourth quarter, with an 11 percent sales increase over Q4 last year.</description>
	<pubDate>21 Feb 2019 05:10:11 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7434</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SpartanNash announces fourth quarter and fiscal year 2018 financial results</title>
	<description>&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fourth Quarter Net Sales Increase Driven by Continued Strong Growth in Food Distribution Segment of 4.7%&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>21 Feb 2019 04:49:04 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7430</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Village Farms International’s common shares to commence trading on NASDAQ on February 21, 2019.</title>
	<description>Village Farms International, Inc.,&#160;has announced that its common shares will commence trading on the Nasdaq Capital Market under the symbol “VFF” on Thursday, February 21, 2019. Village Farms’ common shares will continue to be listed and trade on the Toronto Stock Exchange (TSX), also under the symbol “VFF”.</description>
	<pubDate>21 Feb 2019 04:32:46 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7426</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Small California avocado crop will stay West this year</title>
	<description>With California projected to harvest its second smallest avocado crop in the last 40 years, only West Coast buyers may be able to have California fruit to sell this year.</description>
	<pubDate>21 Feb 2019 03:08:58 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7423</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>NGA preview: taking on competition</title>
	<description>The retail and wholesale supplier members of the National Grocers Association may not have the power and influence of the large national chains, but there’s a benefit to being smaller and nimbler.</description>
	<pubDate>21 Feb 2019 11:51:52 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7417</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Lime prices could double by Easter</title>
	<description>Lime prices from Mexico have risen in the past few weeks, and suppliers say they could double by Easter, in two months.</description>
	<pubDate>20 Feb 2019 02:56:26 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7410</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>OPS workshop explores wholesalers’ role in organic</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE The role of wholesalers and distributors of organic fresh produce continues to change as the dynamics of production, supply chain and consumers evolve. Three of North America&#39;s largest and most progressive wholesale distributors will discuss the changing landscape, opportunities and challenges they see for organic fresh produce at the Organic Produce Summit, July 10-11 in Monterey, CA.</description>
	<pubDate>20 Feb 2019 02:05:30 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7398</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Wholesum eclipses 3 million dollar mark to empower worker communities through Fair Trade</title>
	<description>Wholesum™ reflects on the deep impact that the Fair Trade Program has had on its farms and employees. A monumental achievement, the community development funds generated by the sales of Wholesum’s Fair Trade Certified produce has surpassed the 3 million-dollar mark in just five years, with over 1 million dollars being raised in 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>20 Feb 2019 12:17:39 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7391</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Kroger and Ocado add two more high-tech fulfillment centers</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE The Kroger Co., Cincinnati, America&#39;s largest grocery retailer, and Ocado, one of the world&#39;s largest dedicated online grocery retailers, today announced Central Florida and Mid-Atlantic as the newly-named regions for America&#39;s next two customer fulfillment centers (CFC).</description>
	<pubDate>19 Feb 2019 02:47:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7360</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>E-Commerce helps Walmart grow in Q4</title>
	<description>Bentonville, AR-based Walmart reported a slight rise in fourth quarter revenue over last year, but its e-commerce continues strong growth with a 43-percent rise in the quarter.</description>
	<pubDate>19 Feb 2019 01:26:24 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7355</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Del Monte sales up in 2018, but profitability falls</title>
	<description>Fresh Del Monte Produce Inc. reported higher sales in 2018 but lower gross profit than the previous year.</description>
	<pubDate>19 Feb 2019 11:29:43 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7352</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>America&#39;s best supermarkets have this in common</title>
	<description>How can a retailer that’s only been in the U.S. for less than two years make a list of America’s “best” supermarkets?</description>
	<pubDate>18 Feb 2019 04:22:31 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7346</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Surviving failure makes you stronger</title>
	<description>Failure is a natural part of business.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Feb 2019 03:40:39 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7342</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Wegmans lowers prices, citing SNAP concerns</title>
	<description>Potatoes, onions, lettuce, grapes and salad mix are among more than a dozen grocery staples Wegmans Food Markets is offering with lower prices following the government shutdown.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Feb 2019 02:58:57 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7337</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Apples soar into new year with rising retail prices</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;&#160;&lt;/strong&gt;The Polar Vortex blasted many U.S. states in January 2019, but it didn’t hinder apple category performance according to Stemilt Growers and their latest Fruit Tracker™ Fast Facts &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ixa6lmK_-xw&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&quot;&gt;video analysis&lt;/a&gt;.&#160; Dollars were up on apples sold in January while the volume was similar to January 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Feb 2019 10:48:52 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7313</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Wonderful aims at parents for new Halos snacking campaign</title>
	<description>LOS ANGELES (February 12, 2019) – Wonderful Halos, America’s No. 1 most loved healthy snack brand, launched a new integrated marketing campaign this season, “The Checks-All-The-Boxes Box,” to encourage parents to choose sweet, seedless, easy-to-peel Halos mandarins as the perfect solution when assigned the sometimes daunting task of snack duty.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Feb 2019 04:16:53 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7276</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>US Foods reports fourth quarter and fiscal year 2018 earnings</title>
	<description>US Foods Holding Corp., &lt;b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;one of the largest foodservice distributors in the United States, has announced results for the fourth quarter and full fiscal year 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Feb 2019 01:33:42 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7267</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SAGARPA changes name to SADER</title>
	<description>As Mexico’s equivalent of the U.S. Department of Agriculture adjusts to its new name and direction, it’s also starting four new programs this year.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Feb 2019 01:30:05 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7265</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>XPO Logistics announces fourth quarter and full year 2018 results</title>
	<description>XPO Logistics, Inc.,&#160;has announced financial results for the fourth quarter and full year 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Feb 2019 01:02:00 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7260</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>FDA offers industry guidance after completing E. coli investigation</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE The Food and Drug Administration &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fda.gov/Food/RecallsOutbreaksEmergencies/Outbreaks/ucm626330.htm&quot;&gt;has completed its investigation&lt;/a&gt; of the multistate outbreak of E. coli O157:H7 illnesses linked to romaine lettuce grown in California in Fall 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Feb 2019 10:20:03 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7257</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Walmart is outpacing Amazon in e-grocery</title>
	<description>Walmart is pulling ahead of Amazon for online grocery shoppers, and I know why.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Feb 2019 08:39:59 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7252</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Produce Reporter Week in Review: February 15, 2019</title>
	<description>Pamela and Greg discuss some of the most engaging content for The Produce Reporter readers this week including:</description>
	<pubDate>14 Feb 2019 09:28:32 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7248</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Retailers, logistics firm among Fortune Best Companies to Work For honorees</title>
	<description>There’s a new name among the Fortune Magazine 100 Best Companies to Work For list, one that’s familiar to many in the fresh produce industry.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Feb 2019 04:31:35 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7231</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA restricts PACA violators in California and New York from operating in produce industry</title>
	<description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) has imposed sanctions on four produce businesses for failure to pay reparation awards issued under the Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act (PACA).</description>
	<pubDate>14 Feb 2019 03:25:31 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7222</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>CPS project looks at Listeria risk for nontraditional salad ingredients</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE As nontraditional ingredients -- such as beet greens, kale, Brussels sprouts and shredded broccoli stalks -- gain popularity in fresh-cut salad mixes, questions have arisen about the potential risk of Listeria monocytogenes growth on them.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Feb 2019 03:17:13 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7219</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>C.H. Robinson names Bob Biesterfeld CEO</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Minneapolis, Minnesota, February 11, 2019&#160;&lt;/strong&gt;— C.H. Robinson (NASDAQ: CHRW) announced today&#160;that Robert (“Bob”) Biesterfeld, currently the Company&#39;s Chief Operating Officer, has been named Chief Executive Officer. As part of a long-planned succession process managed by C.H. Robinson’s Board of Directors, Biesterfeld was named COO in&#160;March 2018. Biesterfeld has also been nominated to stand for election to the C.H. Robinson Board of Directors. Current Chairman and CEO John Wiehoff will remain Chairman of the Board following this succession. Scott Anderson, current C.H. Robinson Board member, will become the Lead Independent Director. All moves will become&#160;effective on May 9, 2019, coinciding with our annual meeting of shareholders.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Feb 2019 11:49:27 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7211</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Radiant Logistics announces results for second fiscal quarter</title>
	<description>Radiant Logistics, Inc., a third-party logistics and multimodal&#160;transportation services company, reported financial results for the three and six months ended December 31, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Feb 2019 10:51:33 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7201</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Fresh launches 2019 produce industry compensation survey</title>
	<description>The United Fresh Produce Association has launched its 2019 Compensation Survey for the fresh produce industry. The data collected will be published in an expansive research report that will assist produce industry employers in understanding critical compensation benchmarks.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Feb 2019 08:55:08 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=7045</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Produce marketers shouldn&#39;t push vegan</title>
	<description>Consumers should eat more fresh fruits and vegetables for their own health and possibly the health of the planet.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Feb 2019 05:14:47 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6966</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Produce price increases trail the rest of the store</title>
	<description>A new report from Jacksonville, FL-based Acosta Inc. shows grocery prices have been increasing steadily over the past five years, thanks to increasing costs from manufacturers.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Feb 2019 04:53:27 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6961</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Oppy focuses on Canadian sales with personnel moves</title>
	<description>In a move to grow Canadian sales, Oppy has promoted David Wazny to sales manager of the team based in the company’s Vancouver, BC headquarters and Colbert Rahal to a newly created role of sales manager of eastern Canada.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Feb 2019 02:02:03 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6796</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Love Beets pairs with Kroger for National Heart Health Month promotion</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;BALA CYNWYD, PA&lt;/strong&gt; – February 12, 2018 – Love Beets, the creators of everyone’s favorite ready-to-eat beets, will celebrate National Heart Health Month with their “Love Your Heart-BEET” campaign during the month of February.&#160; The campaign will span both in-store efforts and digital activations across the Love Beets social platforms with the goal of educating consumers that beets are a great addition to a heart-healthy diet.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Feb 2019 08:57:08 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6786</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Vision Import Group hires industry veteran Tony Mitchell</title>
	<description>Vision Import Group hires industry veteran Tony Mitchell as Vice President of Sales and Business Development.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Feb 2019 08:33:08 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6782</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Whole Foods raises prices on hundreds of items</title>
	<description>Whole Foods plans to raise prices on hundreds of items, going away from its pledge to offer lower prices.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Feb 2019 02:09:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6777</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Trading Tip: Good Arrival – The Sixth Day</title>
	<description>The warranty of suitable shipping condition is at the center of countless disputes and decisions each day. Although there is some devil in the details, the main idea is straightforward enough.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Feb 2019 11:43:04 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6775</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Envy apples are turning heads once again</title>
	<description>Making another appearance at the internationally acclaimed New York Fashion Week (NYFW) last weekend, this time Envy™ apples created even more excitement through a special partnership with Christian Siriano, the innovative young designer of Project Runway fame. Guests of Siriano’s AW19 Runway Show and after party enjoyed an Envy™ apple tasting bar, signature Envy™ cocktail and other tasty treats as Siriano unveiled his latest collection.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Feb 2019 10:15:12 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6766</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>An Apeel-ing experience</title>
	<description>Apeel Sciences sent me a Happy New Year kit of caviar limes grown by Good Land Organics, Santa Barbara, CA, so I decided to do a little test.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Feb 2019 04:53:44 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6764</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>PMA&#39;s Center for Growing Talent names theme for women&#39;s events</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE Newark, Del. – Center for Growing Talent (CGT) is pleased to announce the new theme for Women’s Fresh Perspectives events for 2019: I WILL.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Feb 2019 04:11:10 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6757</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Fresh reboots 2019 June event</title>
	<description>The United Fresh Produce Association will give attendees to its annual June event a new experience this year.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Feb 2019 03:48:43 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6754</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Consumers need evidence of struggles</title>
	<description>Farmers in rural states are filing for bankruptcy at alarming rates, as years of increased input costs and low commodity prices cause these businesses to fail.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Feb 2019 05:00:44 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6735</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Produce Reporter Week in Review: February 8, 2019</title>
	<description>Greg and Pamela discuss popular content with The Produce Reporter subscribers, including:</description>
	<pubDate>08 Feb 2019 04:55:37 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6745</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fresh apple holdings down 12% from 2018</title>
	<description>The February 1 U.S. Holdings report from the USApple Association showed fresh apple holdings are 7% less than the 5-year average, and 12% less than last year.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Feb 2019 04:50:52 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6741</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Ingles Markets, Inc., reports sales and net income for first quarter fiscal 2019</title>
	<description>Ingles Markets, Inc.,&#160;reported higher sales and pretax income for the three months ended December 29, 2018, compared with the three months ended December 30, 2017. Total sales rose 4.7% over the comparative quarters. Pretax income totaled $28.1 million for the quarter ended December 29, 2018, 10.9% higher than pretax income of $25.4 million for the quarter ended December 30, 2017. The December 2017 quarter included a reduction in non-cash deferred tax expense from changes to federal income tax law, resulting in higher net income for the December 2017 quarter compared with the current quarter.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Feb 2019 03:50:45 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6738</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Ingles Markets, Inc., reports sales and net income for first quarter fiscal 2019</title>
	<description>Ingles Markets, Inc.,&#160;reported higher sales and pretax income for the three months ended December 29, 2018, compared with the three months ended December 30, 2017. Total sales rose 4.7% over the comparative quarters. Pretax income totaled $28.1 million for the quarter ended December 29, 2018, 10.9% higher than pretax income of $25.4 million for the quarter ended December 30, 2017. The December 2017 quarter included a reduction in non-cash deferred tax expense from changes to federal income tax law, resulting in higher net income for the December 2017 quarter compared with the current quarter.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Feb 2019 03:50:45 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6738</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA cites Sarita Ranch Provission Inc. for PACA Violations</title>
	<description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) has cited Sarita Ranch Provission Inc., Los Angeles, Calif., for failure to pay for produce.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Feb 2019 03:04:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6719</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Natural Grocers reports Q1 2019 earnings</title>
	<description>&lt;span class=&quot;xn-location&quot;&gt;LAKEWOOD, Colo.&lt;/span&gt;,&#160;&lt;span class=&quot;xn-chron&quot;&gt;Feb. 7, 2019&lt;/span&gt;&#160;/PRNewswire/ --&#160;Natural Grocers by Vitamin Cottage, Inc. (NYSE:&#160;&lt;a href=&quot;http://studio-5.financialcontent.com/prnews?Page=Quote&amp;amp;Ticker=NGVC&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;NGVC&lt;/a&gt;) today announced results for its first quarter of fiscal 2019 ended&#160;&lt;span class=&quot;xn-chron&quot;&gt;December 31, 2018&lt;/span&gt;&#160;and confirmed its outlook for fiscal 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Feb 2019 12:06:17 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6709</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Former Aldi UK executive appointed Lidl US Chairman</title>
	<description>Company Press Release: Arlington, VA – Lidl US announced today that it would welcome Roman Heini to its leadership team as Chairman, effective March 1, 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Feb 2019 11:57:08 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6705</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Recalls at a five-year low, FDA says, as it issues new notification guidance</title>
	<description>Consumers should expect to see more frequent recall notifications as the FDA takes steps to modernize notification and warning procedures.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Feb 2019 11:46:11 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6702</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hype vs. reality</title>
	<description>Thank goodness the Super Bowl is in the rear-view mirror.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Feb 2019 05:00:50 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6675</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>FPAA disappointed in U.S. intent to withdraw from tomato agreement</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE Nogales, AZ—The Fresh Produce Association of the Americas (FPAA) is disappointed to learn that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producebluebook.com/2019/02/07/u-s-plans-to-withdraw-from-suspension-agreement-on-tomatoes-from-mexico/&quot;&gt;Department of Commerce intends to withdraw from the 2013 Tomato Suspension Agreement with Mexico.&lt;/a&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>07 Feb 2019 04:51:10 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6689</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Report from Fruit Logistica 2019</title>
	<description>Fruit Logistica 2019 expected to see 78,000 attendees for the annual event, Feb. 6-8 in Berlin.</description>
	<pubDate>07 Feb 2019 04:34:03 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6687</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The first Aldi/Kohls mashup is now open</title>
	<description>Remember when Batavia, IL-based Aldi Inc. and Menomonee Falls, WI-based Kohls Department Stores floated the idea of a collaboration?</description>
	<pubDate>07 Feb 2019 04:27:19 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6684</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>ProMexico’s Closing… For better or for worse?</title>
	<description>Originally set up in 2007 as a trust fund to promote international trade and investment, ProMexico is now facing its last weeks in operation.</description>
	<pubDate>07 Feb 2019 04:03:45 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6680</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>U.S. plans to withdraw from suspension agreement on tomatoes from Mexico</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE -- On February 6, 2019, the Department of Commerce notified the Mexican signatories to the 2013 Suspension Agreement on Fresh Tomatoes from Mexico that the Department intends to withdraw from the Agreement, consistent with Section VI.B. Section VI.B of the Agreement states that “[t]he signatories or the Department may withdraw from this Agreement upon ninety days written notice to the other party.”</description>
	<pubDate>07 Feb 2019 02:47:53 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6669</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Ag leaders turn focus to USMCA</title>
	<description>With the new Congress settled, President Trump’s State of the Union address and government shutdown all in the past, it’s time for government leaders to pass the U.S.-Mexico-Canada trade agreement, many groups say.</description>
	<pubDate>07 Feb 2019 02:43:26 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6666</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Produce for Better Health Foundation hires new Director of Communications</title>
	<description>Produce for Better Health Foundation (PBH), whose mission is to increase consumers’ consumption of fruits and vegetables for better health, has hired Katie Toulouse as the new Director of Communications.</description>
	<pubDate>07 Feb 2019 02:41:24 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6665</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Will meal kits work without fresh?</title>
	<description>Major meal kit companies are dropping fresh produce in new offerings, and it seems like a good idea – as much as I hate to admit it.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Feb 2019 04:43:41 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6643</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Coastal California rain causes harvest delays</title>
	<description>Rain in the Coastal California growing areas is making it tougher for retailers to get strawberries, celery and various greens.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Feb 2019 03:37:46 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6637</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Echo Global Logistics reports record 2018 Revenue</title>
	<description>Echo Global Logistics, Inc.,&#160;a leading provider of technology-enabled transportation management services, today reported financial results for the quarter and full year ended&#160;December&#160;31, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Feb 2019 03:31:39 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6633</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Meal kit provider Blue Apron strips the meat, produce in new offering</title>
	<description>Company Press Release: NEW YORK--Blue Apron Holdings, Inc. (NYSE: APRN), known for creating incredible meal experiences, today introduced its most flexible culinary innovation to date: Blue Apron Knick Knacks™, a new line of recipe solutions that give consumers the flexibility to combine the protein and produce of their choice with specialty, pre-portioned, refrigerated ingredients and step-by-step recipes to enjoy a delicious meal for two.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Feb 2019 03:29:23 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6631</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Kroger expands Home Chef distribution, offers customization online</title>
	<description>Company Press Release: CINCINNATI&#160;and&#160;CHICAGO,&#160;Feb. 6, 2019&#160;/PRNewswire/ -- The Kroger Co. (NYSE:&#160;&lt;a href=&quot;http://studio-5.financialcontent.com/prnews?Page=Quote&amp;amp;Ticker=KR&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;KR&lt;/a&gt;) and Home Chef announced today the introduction of retail meal kits to new cities, bringing the weekly rotating meal solution to 500 additional Kroger Family of Stores across the country. Additionally,&#160;&lt;a href=&quot;https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;amp;l=en&amp;amp;o=2367858-1&amp;amp;h=402645819&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.homechef.com%2F&amp;amp;a=homechef.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;homechef.com&lt;/a&gt;&#160;has launched a customizable meal kit feature for online orders, allowing customers to have more flexibility in deciding what&#39;s for dinner by providing the choice to change and upgrade recipe ingredients. The feature—the first among leading meal kit brands—offers unprecedented variety for customers.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Feb 2019 03:19:03 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6626</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Wholesum prepares for another season of fair trade blueberries</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;COMPANY PRESS RELEASE&lt;/strong&gt; -- Wholesum prepares for a very fruitful month for organic Chilean blueberries. Availability of organic Chilean blueberries has been on an upward trend and will have the highest spike between February and March of 2019 for Wholesum.&#160;The bulk of organic blueberries will come from their partner grower Valles del Sur SpA in Vilcun, Chile which has been fair trade certified by Fair Trade USA since 2018 and through FLOCERT since 2016. Fair Trade product from Chile is a cornerstone of Wholesum’s blueberry program.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Feb 2019 03:08:46 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6623</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Giant to open three more small format Heirloom Markets in 2019</title>
	<description>&lt;span class=&quot;xn-location&quot;&gt;Press Release --&lt;/span&gt;&#160;&lt;u&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://c212.net/c/link/?t=0&amp;amp;l=en&amp;amp;o=2367234-1&amp;amp;h=1320719701&amp;amp;u=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.giantfoodstores.com%2F&amp;amp;a=GIANT+Food+Stores&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow noopener&quot;&gt;GIANT Food Stores&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&#160;today announced plans to expand its strategic growth in the city of&#160;&lt;span class=&quot;xn-location&quot;&gt;Philadelphia&lt;/span&gt;&#160;with the opening of three more GIANT Heirloom Market™ stores during 2019. Building on the success of the first location of this innovative urban store concept in the Graduate Hospital area, the new GIANT Heirloom Market stores will bring a format and assortment specially curated for each of the unique&#160;&lt;span class=&quot;xn-location&quot;&gt;Philadelphia&lt;/span&gt;neighborhoods of University City, Northern Liberties and&#160;&lt;span class=&quot;xn-location&quot;&gt;Queen Village&lt;/span&gt;, with local vendor partnerships lending authentic and familiar flavors.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Feb 2019 11:55:21 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6620</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Viva Fresh names &quot;Hero Food&quot; chef, author keynote speaker</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Pres Release -- Mission, Texas: February 6, 2018: &#160;&#160;&lt;/strong&gt;Seamus Mullen, award-winning New York chef, cookbook author and health and wellness expert will share his own personal healing journey during Viva Fresh Expo’s Keynote Luncheon on Friday, April 26 at the JW Marriott Hill Country Resort in San Antonio, Texas.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Feb 2019 11:47:25 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6616</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA awards over $2.85 million to California Table Grape Commission</title>
	<description>The California Table Grape Commission&#160;has been awarded over $2.85 million as part of the USDA Agricultural Trade Promotion (ATP) program. ATP is intended to help mitigate the damage done to U.S. agricultural products by tariffs imposed by multiple countries. Over $200 million was allocated to organizations throughout the country. Of the 17 California-based ATP recipients, the commission ranked third in total dollars allocated.</description>
	<pubDate>06 Feb 2019 10:59:37 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6769</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA restricts PACA violators in CA, FL, and GA from operating in produce industry</title>
	<description>&lt;div class=&quot;field field--name-field-contact-info field--type-node-reference field--label-above&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>06 Feb 2019 09:52:36 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6696</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Performance Food Group Company reports second quarter 2019 results</title>
	<description>&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vistar delivers double-digit sales growth and&#160;strong cash flow;&#160;r&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;b&gt;eaffirms 2019 full-year fiscal outlook.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/em&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>06 Feb 2019 09:47:29 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6659</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SNAPSHOT: Organic price premium narrows at retail</title>
	<description>I saw an article from the Washington Post that suggests supplies of organic items are catching up to conventional, helping narrow the price gap.</description>
	<pubDate>05 Feb 2019 08:24:13 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6604</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>PBH offers retail pairings program</title>
	<description>The Produce for Better Health Foundation will partner with at least five national retail chains this year for month-long pairing promotions.</description>
	<pubDate>05 Feb 2019 04:53:23 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6596</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Echo Global Logistics names Paula Frey as chief human resources officer</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE -- Echo Global Logistics, Inc.,&#160;a leading provider of technology-enabled transportation and supply chain management services, announced today that Paula Frey has been named Chief Human Resources Officer.</description>
	<pubDate>05 Feb 2019 04:33:32 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6592</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Dan Stark joins PMA as Chief Content Officer</title>
	<description>NEWS RELEASE Newark, Del. – To amplify and enhance the value of content and education that the Produce Marketing Association provides the produce and floral industries, PMA has named the organization’s first Chief Content Officer. Dan Stark joins PMA in January and will be responsible for providing leadership to the organization’s marketing, communications and education efforts.</description>
	<pubDate>05 Feb 2019 03:30:28 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6587</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Be careful with produce markdowns -- especially avocados</title>
	<description>My local retailer, San Antonio-based H-E-B, has been offering a house brand of so-called ugly produce under the Inner Beauties label for a while, and now they’re piloting a markdown program under the same name.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Feb 2019 09:37:39 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6579</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hy-Vee pilots food waste reduction app</title>
	<description>WEST DES MOINES, Iowa (Feb. 1, 2019) — Hy-Vee is announcing a new pilot program with Flashfood, the first and only mobile app that partners with grocers to help reduce food waste by allowing shoppers to browse and purchase food items approaching their “best before” date at significantly reduced prices. Starting today, the Flashfood App and program will be available at both Madison Hy-Vee locations as well as the Fitchburg Hy-Vee store in Wisconsin.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Feb 2019 09:04:22 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6575</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Beer giants look to organic</title>
	<description>Every time people measure it, organic produce sales growth outpaces conventional growth.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Feb 2019 04:03:39 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6544</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Fresh opens application period for Produce Industry Leadership Program</title>
	<description>Press Release – The application period is now open for the 25&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; class of the United Fresh Produce Industry Leadership Program. Since its launch in 1995, more than 250 produce industry members have graduated from this exclusive program, thanks to the generous support of founding sponsor Corteva Agriscience.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Feb 2019 01:43:13 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6540</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Fresh promotes Mary Coppola to Vice President, Market &amp;amp; Communications</title>
	<description>Press Release – The United Fresh Produce Association has promoted Mary Coppola to Vice President, Marketing &amp;amp; Communications. Coppola joined the association in the fall of 2014, spearheading the organization’s marketing and communications efforts.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Feb 2019 01:16:43 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6534</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Sysco reports second quarter 2019 results</title>
	<description>COMPANY FINANCIAL RELEASE --&#160;Sysco Corporation&#160;announced financial results for its 13-week second fiscal quarter ended December&#160;29, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Feb 2019 09:37:43 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6656</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Retailers should find promotable citrus crop</title>
	<description>Heading toward spring, citrus supplies should be as promotable as ever, high in quality and volume, but smaller than normal on sizing.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Feb 2019 05:30:09 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6521</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Apeel and Nature&#39;s Pride partner to fight food waste in Europe</title>
	<description>NEWS RELEASE&lt;span style=&quot;float: none;background-color: transparent;color: #333333;cursor: text;font-family: Georgia,&#39;Times New Roman&#39;,&#39;Bitstream Charter&#39;,Times,serif;font-size: 16px;font-style: normal;font-variant: normal;font-weight: 400;letter-spacing: normal;text-align: left;text-decoration: none;text-indent: 0px&quot;&gt;—&lt;/span&gt;Apeel Sciences, a World Economic Forum Technology Pioneer and one of Time Magazine’s 50 Genius Companies, and Nature’s Pride, Europe’s leader in avocados and mangos with a focus on sustainability, have officially joined forces.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Feb 2019 05:00:36 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6515</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Consider this when selling your business</title>
	<description>Selling a business is no easy task.</description>
	<pubDate>03 Feb 2019 06:00:03 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6518</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>An Ode to 365 by Whole Foods Market</title>
	<description>&amp;nbsp;</description>
	<pubDate>01 Feb 2019 04:55:07 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6525</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>An Ode to 365 by Whole Foods Market</title>
	<description>&amp;nbsp;</description>
	<pubDate>01 Feb 2019 04:55:07 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6525</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Publix Vice President of Manufacturing to retire</title>
	<description>After 38 years of dedicated service, Vice President of Manufacturing, Jeff Stephens, announced his decision to retire, effective May 1, 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Feb 2019 04:19:19 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6550</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Seneca Foods reports third quarter results</title>
	<description>Seneca Foods Corporation announced financial results for the third quarter and nine months ended December 29, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Feb 2019 04:11:10 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6589</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Amazon.com announces 2018 fourth quarter sales</title>
	<description>FINANCIAL RELEASE -- Amazon.com, Inc., announced financial results for its fourth quarter ended December&#160;31, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Feb 2019 02:08:20 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6510</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>H-E-B restaurants launch Hunger Stops Here food bank fundraiser</title>
	<description>Press Release -- Throughout February, when Texans enjoy a delicious meal at one of H-E-B’s many family-friendly restaurants, H-E-B will donate a portion of each sale to help combat hunger in the Lone Star State. The effort is part of its annual Hunger Stops Here campaign, a charitable event benefiting Texas food banks and organizations.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Feb 2019 11:49:28 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6490</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Wish Farms, Monte Packaging to host 6th annual Strawberry Picking Challenge</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Press Release&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&#160;&lt;/strong&gt;– Wish Farms and Monte Package Company present the sixth annual Strawberry Picking Challenge on February 8&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; and 9&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;. The charity event raises funds for the Redlands Christian Migrant Association, inviting guests out to the Plant City farm for a day of strawberry picking and entertainment.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Feb 2019 11:42:49 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6478</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Produce Reporter Week in Review: February 1, 2019</title>
	<description>While much of North America suffered from the polar vortex, Blue Book&#39;s Director of Media Development Greg Johnson and Retail Editor Pamela Riemenschneider discuss how the cold affected crops and some retail developments. Here are some of the top stories of the week:</description>
	<pubDate>01 Feb 2019 10:02:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6451</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>PMA scheduled for SXSW session</title>
	<description>The Produce Marketing Association attended last year’s South by Southwest conference in Austin, TX, to learn and raise awareness for the role fresh produce and floral play in food culture.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Feb 2019 09:48:19 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6446</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>See Avocados from Mexico’s Super Bowl ads before the Big Game</title>
	<description>What do avocados and dogs have in common?</description>
	<pubDate>01 Feb 2019 09:34:47 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6443</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>No delivery? No problem – if you’re Trader Joe’s</title>
	<description>Business Insider is reporting Monrovia, CA-based Trader Joe’s is ending delivery, with no plans to pick it back up.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Feb 2019 09:18:34 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6439</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Organic again drives produce department growth</title>
	<description>News Release -- In a year when total grocery store dollar growth only reached two percent, organic fresh produce once again surpassed the status quo according to new information released by the Organic Produce Network and Nielsen.</description>
	<pubDate>31 Jan 2019 09:38:52 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6421</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>UNFI sues Goldman Sachs for misconduct in Supervalu acquisition</title>
	<description>PROVIDENCE, R.I. &amp;amp; MINNEAPOLIS--(BUSINESS WIRE)--United Natural Foods, Inc. (UNFI), North America&#39;s premier food wholesaler delivering the widest variety of products to a diverse and expansive customer base, today filed a multi-count lawsuit in the Supreme Court of the State of New York against Goldman Sachs Group, Inc. and its subsidiaries to recover damages and recoup what UNFI believes are the Bank’s ill-gotten gains stemming from its improper conduct during the period in which it advised UNFI on the $2.9 billion acquisition of Supervalu INC.</description>
	<pubDate>31 Jan 2019 09:30:43 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6419</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>What the numbers tell us about potato and onion trends</title>
	<description>Potatoes are the top vegetable crop in the United States, according to the U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA).</description>
	<pubDate>31 Jan 2019 06:01:26 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6235</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>New organic event aims to educate New England retailers</title>
	<description>The New England Produce Council and the Organic Produce Network have partnered to start a one-day education event that plans to better educate Eastern retailers about organic produce.</description>
	<pubDate>30 Jan 2019 03:34:24 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6415</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Stemilt&#39;s analysis shows strong demand for apples</title>
	<description>NEWS RELEASE – The latest Stemilt Fruit Tracker Fast Facts video analysis of Nielsen scan data signals a strengthening apple category, despite a slow start to apple sales in the new crop year and a national apple crop that’s down considerably from 2017.</description>
	<pubDate>30 Jan 2019 02:30:09 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6409</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Chef’d buyer relaunches retail meal kits – with a processed twist</title>
	<description>Just over six months after buying embattled meal kit company Chef’d, True Food Innovations says it is launching new products aimed at retail.</description>
	<pubDate>30 Jan 2019 12:18:03 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6407</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Trading Tip: Authority of an employee</title>
	<description>You recently settled a transaction with a salesman, let’s call him Sam, who you just found out is no longer employed by the seller, SellCo.</description>
	<pubDate>29 Jan 2019 05:42:57 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6400</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>What makes a grocer “the best?”</title>
	<description>A lot of stories about retailers being named “the best” or “most admired” or “favorite” come across my inbox. The past few weeks have been exceptionally busy in this department.</description>
	<pubDate>29 Jan 2019 05:11:36 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6394</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Church Brothers Farms acquires commodity vegetable business from Growers Express</title>
	<description>&lt;i&gt;Deal Includes Licensing Agreement for Green Giant™ Fresh Commodity Vegetables&lt;/i&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>29 Jan 2019 04:54:45 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6392</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Brinker International reports second quarter results</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Brinker International, Inc.,&#160;announced results for the fiscal second quarter ended December&#160;26, 2018.&lt;/strong&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>29 Jan 2019 04:38:35 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6562</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>An avocado too big to believe</title>
	<description>How much guacamole do you think a six-pound avocado would make?</description>
	<pubDate>29 Jan 2019 04:09:02 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6390</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hormel Foods announces promotion of James Sheehan to Executive VP &amp;amp; CFO</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE -- Hormel Foods Corporation, a global branded food company, announced today that James N. Sheehan has advanced to executive vice president and chief financial officer.&#160; The advancement was effective January 29, 2019.&#160; Sheehan previously held the role of senior vice president and chief financial officer for the company.&#160; As executive vice president and chief financial officer for Hormel Foods, Sheehan oversees the company&#39;s financial enterprise including accounting, information technology, internal audit, investor relations, corporate tax and treasury.</description>
	<pubDate>29 Jan 2019 01:05:06 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6502</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Hormel Foods announces promotion of James Sheehan to Executive VP &amp;amp; CFO</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE -- Hormel Foods Corporation, a global branded food company, announced today that James N. Sheehan has advanced to executive vice president and chief financial officer.&#160; The advancement was effective January 29, 2019.&#160; Sheehan previously held the role of senior vice president and chief financial officer for the company.&#160; As executive vice president and chief financial officer for Hormel Foods, Sheehan oversees the company&#39;s financial enterprise including accounting, information technology, internal audit, investor relations, corporate tax and treasury.</description>
	<pubDate>29 Jan 2019 01:05:06 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6502</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Ahold Delhaize’s newest urban concept includes an on-demand “produce chef”</title>
	<description>Giant Food Stores, a division of Netherlands-based Ahold Delhaize held the grand opening of its newest concept, the Giant Heirloom Market on January 25.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Jan 2019 03:18:20 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6350</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Sysco to acquire Waugh Foods, Inc.</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE&#160;-- Sysco Corporation,&#160;the leading global foodservice distribution company, announced it has entered into a definitive agreement to acquire Waugh Foods, Inc., a leading&#160;Illinois&#160;broadline distributor with approximately&#160;$40 million&#160;in annual sales.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Jan 2019 02:43:13 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6387</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>California Citrus Mutual names new CEO</title>
	<description>Executive vice president Casey Creamer will be promoted to president and CEO Feb. 1 at the California Citrus Mutual, as longtime leader Joel Nelsen narrows his responsibility.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Jan 2019 02:22:30 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6346</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Satur Farms recall expands to Whole Foods prepared foods</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Press Release --&lt;/strong&gt; In response to a recall by Satur Farms, Whole Foods Market is voluntarily recalling various prepared foods items in eight states containing baby spinach because of a potential contamination of&#160;&lt;em&gt;Salmonella&lt;/em&gt;.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Jan 2019 10:28:10 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6339</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Chilean peaches, nectarines, plums recalled due to listeria find</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Press Release --&lt;/strong&gt; Jac. Vandenberg, Inc. of Yonkers, New York is recalling 1,727 cartons of Fresh Peaches, 1,207 cartons of Fresh Nectarines and 365 cartons of Fresh Plums because they have the potential to be contaminated with&#160;&lt;em&gt;Listeria monocytogenes&lt;/em&gt;, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people, and others with weakened immune systems. Although healthy individuals may suffer only short-term symptoms such as high fever, severe headache, stiffness, nausea, abdominal pain and diarrhea, Listeria infection can cause miscarriages and stillbirths among pregnant women.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Jan 2019 09:03:11 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6332</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Shutdown postpones FPAA Spring Policy Summit</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Press Release&#160;&lt;/strong&gt;— The Fresh Produce Association of the Americas is postponing the previously announced Spring Policy Summit, which had been scheduled for March 19-20, 2019, in Tubac, AZ.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Jan 2019 08:30:07 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6323</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The value of a name</title>
	<description>Many years ago, a produce company sold its assets to an investor.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Jan 2019 06:00:50 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6290</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Viva Fresh Open continues to expand in 2019</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Press Release:&#160;&lt;/strong&gt;Register now for the 5th annual Viva Fresh Open! Presented by BEBO Distributing, Inc. and Wonderful Citrus, this year’s tournament promises to provide a world class experience, offering networking and entertainment; as well as a great opportunity to support the industry.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Jan 2019 04:28:26 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6319</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>A chat with Leah Halverson of 10 Acre Marketing</title>
	<description>I took time to talk with Leah Halverson, who recently launched a new venture, 10 Acre Marketing.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Jan 2019 03:36:45 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6311</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>A chat with Leah Halverson of 10 Acre Marketing</title>
	<description>I took time to talk with Leah Halverson, who recently launched a new venture, 10 Acre Marketing.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Jan 2019 03:36:45 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6311</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Control your own integrity and quality</title>
	<description>During this government shutdown, it’s tempting to conclude that food is less safe because government inspections aren’t taking place.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Jan 2019 01:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6287</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Produce Reporter Week in Review: January 25, 2019</title>
	<description>Blue Book Services Director of Media Development talks with Retail Editor Pamela Riemenschneider about the top stories for The Produce Reporter readers this week, including:</description>
	<pubDate>25 Jan 2019 10:39:54 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6282</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>FPAA postpones Spring Policy Summit</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE -- The Fresh Produce Association of the Americas is postponing the previously-announced Spring Policy Summit, which had been scheduled for March 19-20, 2019, in Tubac, AZ.</description>
	<pubDate>25 Jan 2019 08:51:28 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6327</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA continues restrictions of PACA violator in South Dakota</title>
	<description>USDA RELEASE&#160;– The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) has imposed sanctions on a produce business for failure to pay reparation awards issued under the Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act (PACA).</description>
	<pubDate>24 Jan 2019 02:17:35 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6295</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Spinach, mesclun recalled in New York, Florida after positive salmonella test</title>
	<description>Company News -- Satur Farms, 3705 Alvah&#39;s Lane, Cutchogue, NY 11935 is voluntarily recalling Baby Spinach and Mesclun with the specific lot numbers listed below because it has the potential to be contaminated with&#160;&lt;em&gt;Salmonella&lt;/em&gt;, an organism which can cause serious and sometimes fatal infections in young children, frail or elderly people and others with weakened immune systems. Healthy persons infected with&#160;&lt;em&gt;Salmonella&lt;/em&gt;&#160;often experience fever, diarrhea (which may be bloody), nausea, vomiting and abdominal pain. In rare circumstances, infection with&#160;&lt;em&gt;Salmonella&lt;/em&gt;&#160;can result in the organism getting into the bloodstream and producing more severe illnesses such as arterial infections (i.e. aneurysms), endocarditis and arthritis. The following product was distributed in New York and Florida through retail stores.</description>
	<pubDate>24 Jan 2019 01:47:47 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6276</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Starbucks reports 2019 first quarter fiscal results</title>
	<description>FINANCIAL RELEASE -- Starbucks Corporation&#160;reported financial results for its 13-week fiscal first quarter ended December&#160;30, 2018. GAAP results in fiscal 2019 and fiscal 2018 include items which are excluded from non-GAAP results. Please refer to the reconciliation of GAAP measures to non-GAAP measures at the end of this release for more information.</description>
	<pubDate>24 Jan 2019 01:41:49 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6506</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Celery, lettuce growers overcome cold mornings in the desert</title>
	<description>Despite some early morning frost in the Yuma, AZ, and Coachella and Imperial Valleys, celery and lettuce shippers report strong quality and project higher volume the last week of January.</description>
	<pubDate>24 Jan 2019 01:27:04 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6272</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Veggies Inc. to start care packages under &quot;Mexico Cares&quot; program</title>
	<description>COMPANY PRESS RELEASE--Veggies Inc. in cooperation with Mexican growers will start packing “care packages” under the &lt;b&gt;&quot;Mexico Cares&quot;&lt;/b&gt; program to help feed the employees affected by the government shutdown.&#160; The packages will be distributed in Nogales, Tucson, and Phoenix until the shutdown is over and they start getting paid.</description>
	<pubDate>24 Jan 2019 10:23:48 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6263</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA restricts PACA violators in Florida and New York from operating in produce industry</title>
	<description>The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) has imposed sanctions on three produce businesses for failure to pay reparation awards issued under the Perishable Agricultural Commodities Act (PACA).</description>
	<pubDate>23 Jan 2019 04:51:20 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6257</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Government shutdown frustrates organic industry</title>
	<description>The organic food industry made great gains in the 2018 farm bill, but the ongoing government shutdown puts several benefits on hold.</description>
	<pubDate>23 Jan 2019 04:49:56 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6255</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USApple selects 2019 Young Apple Leaders</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE--The U.S. Apple Association (USApple) has announced its class of 2019 Young Apple Leaders. Twenty-two accomplished and aspiring young women and men were selected by the organization to join with, and learn from, USApple leaders as they advocate on important issues impacting growers and the $15 billion per year apple industry.</description>
	<pubDate>23 Jan 2019 04:42:34 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6250</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Salmonella find prompts Vietnamese chili recall in Canada</title>
	<description>An undisclosed amount of red chili peppers grown in Vietnam are being recalled in Canada due to a possible salmonella contamination.</description>
	<pubDate>23 Jan 2019 04:28:41 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6243</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Trader Joe’s favorite produce item isn’t bananas anymore</title>
	<description>Over the past 10 years, Monrovia, CA-based Trader Joe’s has polled customers on their favorite items to buy in-store.</description>
	<pubDate>23 Jan 2019 11:25:11 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6209</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>New Seasons Market announces new leadership structure</title>
	<description>Company Press Release &#160;– January 22, 2019 – New Seasons Market, the world’s first B Corp grocery store, announced today a new executive leadership structure to support the company’s continued investment in staff, customers, partners and local communities.</description>
	<pubDate>23 Jan 2019 09:19:40 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6193</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Stemilt hosts Chef Ethan Stowell for Pinata Apple inspired event</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Company Press Release:&lt;/strong&gt; Stemilt took a page out of its mission statement by delighting its team members through a special meet-and-greet event with its spokeschef, Ethan Stowell, an award-winning chef based in Seattle, WA. The event was held last week at the company’s Fresh Center headquarters and is part of an ongoing partnership between chef Ethan and Stemilt to deepen the farm-to-table connection.</description>
	<pubDate>23 Jan 2019 09:17:52 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6191</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>New Seasons Market announces new leadership structure</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: medium&quot;&gt;Neighborhood grocer well-positioned &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size: medium&quot;&gt;for next phase of company growth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>22 Jan 2019 03:09:57 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6238</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Grocery delivery still needs a human touch</title>
	<description>Am I the only one who thinks picking my produce from a driverless car is an absurd – and unnecessary – advancement in technology?</description>
	<pubDate>22 Jan 2019 03:09:52 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6154</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>CPMA welcomes new Canada Food Guide</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE -- The Canadian Produce Marketing Association (CPMA) and Canadian Public Health Association (CPHA) welcome the positive changes announced today in Health Canada’s unveiling of the updated &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.msgapp.com/jc.aspx?d=DXGM2DUCGAIAJYDXTFZ2KQBMNBH7UKDFXMVCULHJR4L6HO53PL5CNE6JXRA7BPLTQMAVL6HD4D3APDILPTL73S7QFO5XMHANAQPD2DCYXVJUR2JUHUVU6IUPZTUTKE7HQZSNCQOWYFMS22VL5IYW5JLM3FNXWEMJXNVZ2IZXCTLBBA3CPG27Q7AB&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Ffood-guide.canada.ca%2Fen%2F&quot;&gt;Canada Food Guide&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
	<pubDate>22 Jan 2019 11:31:50 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6150</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Texas A&amp;amp;M researcher receives honor</title>
	<description>Press Release – Dr. Bhimu Patil, director of the&#160;Vegetable and Fruit Improvement Center at Texas A&amp;amp;M University in College Station, has been named a Foreign Fellow by the Horticultural Society of India.</description>
	<pubDate>21 Jan 2019 05:03:58 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6128</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Meal kit delivery Sun Basket launches 5-minute salads</title>
	<description>PRESS RELEASE --&#160;Sun Basket,&#160;a leading healthy meal delivery service, today announced their latest innovation: Organic 5-minute salads. The easy-to-assemble salads, created by Sun Basket Co-Founder Chef&#160;Justine Kelly, feature organic ingredients, including&#160;Sun Basket&#39;s&#160;delicious dressings and fresh greens from&#160;organicgirl, a premium salad greens producer.</description>
	<pubDate>21 Jan 2019 04:54:29 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6124</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Produce goes back to bulk in retail plastic-reduction efforts</title>
	<description>A United Kingdom-based retailer is testing a plastic-free produce department at one of its stores, along with measures across the whole banner, to reduce single-use plastic.</description>
	<pubDate>21 Jan 2019 04:42:06 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6121</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Are you a growth or value CEO?</title>
	<description>If you are familiar with stock-picking, you know there are two predominant theories of investing—growth and value.</description>
	<pubDate>21 Jan 2019 07:00:05 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6094</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Two reasons Honeycrisp will continue to dominate</title>
	<description>GRAND JUNCTION, CO—Did Honeycrisp peak?</description>
	<pubDate>18 Jan 2019 04:11:24 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6096</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Media spreads food safety fear during government shutdown</title>
	<description>Industry advocates are fighting back against consumer media recommendations that consumers avoid many foods during the government shutdown, including fresh fruits and vegetables.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Jan 2019 01:50:13 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6091</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Produce industry applauds Governor Ducey’s commitment to Arizona jobs</title>
	<description>&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: #000000;font-family: Calibri&quot;&gt;A strategic port infrastructure investment may yield 200 more jobs for Arizona.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>18 Jan 2019 11:04:20 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6144</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Produce Reporter Week in Review: January 18, 2019</title>
	<description>Greg and Pamela discuss the most engaging topics for The Produce Reporter readers this week, including:</description>
	<pubDate>18 Jan 2019 10:52:34 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6088</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Colorado recap: food safety, retail trends and data top grower concerns</title>
	<description>GRAND JUNCTION, CO – I don’t know if you know this, but I’m big in Colorado.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Jan 2019 10:47:32 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6084</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Strong retail demand bumps up onion market</title>
	<description>Domestic onion shippers are coming off a hot couple of weeks and expect strong demand well into February.</description>
	<pubDate>17 Jan 2019 04:41:17 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6059</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Strong retail demand bumps up onion market</title>
	<description>Domestic onion shippers are coming off a hot couple of weeks and expect strong demand well into February.</description>
	<pubDate>17 Jan 2019 04:41:17 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6059</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Weight Watchers creates meal line for Hy-Vee stores</title>
	<description>NEW YORK /PRNewswire/ -- WW (Weight Watchers reimagined) today introduces new WW Fresh quick-prep meals, which are chef-inspired, nutritionist-approved and ready-to-eat in 10 minutes or less, currently rolling out at more than 200 Hy-Vee grocery store locations across the Midwest.</description>
	<pubDate>17 Jan 2019 01:16:22 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6056</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>CPS announces &quot;Innovation Challenge&quot; grant - GRABIT</title>
	<description>The Center for Produce Safety has announced $500,000 is available to fund the center&#39;s first Innovation Challenge. Dave Corsi, chair of the CPS Board of Directors stated, &quot;This is an invitation and opportunity for technology innovators to develop, refine and focus their solutions to meet a critical industry need; identifying evidence or conditions where cross contamination can take place in our growing environments. This program, currently termed GRABIT - (Grower&#39;s Risk Assessment Biomarkers Investigative Tool)&#160;is designed to bring tools to the supply chain to manage risk and meet the CPS mission: &lt;em&gt;Fund the science, find solutions and fuel the change&lt;/em&gt;.&quot;</description>
	<pubDate>16 Jan 2019 02:56:39 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6038</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Stop &amp;amp; Shop to offer driverless vehicles this spring</title>
	<description>QUINCY, MA, Jan. 16, 2019 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Today, Stop &amp;amp; Shop announced that it will launch driverless grocery vehicles in the Greater Boston area beginning in Spring 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>16 Jan 2019 11:44:53 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=6024</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>GoodFarms™ receives &quot;Communitas Award for Excellence&quot; in corporate social responsibility</title>
	<description>COMPANY&#160; RELEASE – &lt;strong&gt;GoodFarms&lt;/strong&gt;, the consumer-facing, ethical-positioned brand from &lt;strong&gt;Andrew &amp;amp; Williamson Fresh Produce&lt;/strong&gt;, has received recognition for its social responsibility efforts with the 2018 Communitas Award. This award program seeks to honor those special companies, organizations and individuals that are changing the way they do business to benefit their employees, communities and environment.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Jan 2019 02:47:09 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5977</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>OPS 2019 registration opens</title>
	<description>The 2019 Organic Produce Summit&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.organicproducesummit.com/&quot;&gt; has opened registration&lt;/a&gt; for the July 10-11 event in Monterey, CA.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Jan 2019 01:30:25 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5974</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Be careful linking your brand to a cause</title>
	<description>No.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Jan 2019 11:15:44 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5967</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Texas vegetable industry mourns loss of 1015 Supersweet onion pioneer</title>
	<description>COLLEGE STATION – Dr. Leonard Pike, a Texas A&amp;amp;M AgriLife Research scientist who pioneered the 1015 Supersweet onion and the Aggie maroon Beta Sweet carrot, along with a string of other vegetables that contributed billions to the Texas economy, died Jan. 12. He was 78.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Jan 2019 08:43:00 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5963</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>What does Target&#39;s new head of food say about the company&#39;s future?</title>
	<description>Minneapolis-based Target Corp. reported strong holiday sales, along with key executive changes, including naming a new president of food and beverage.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Jan 2019 05:32:51 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5956</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Watch out for Marty, the googly-eyed retail robot</title>
	<description>Company Press Release -- Nearly 500 robots will be coming to the stores of Ahold Delhaize USA brands Stop &amp;amp; Shop and Giant/Martin’s, marking one of the largest deployments of robotics innovation in the U.S. grocery industry. The rollout stems from a partnership between&#160;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.retailbusinessservices.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Retail Business Services&lt;/a&gt;&#160;– the services company of Ahold Delhaize USA – and&#160;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.badger-technologies.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Badger Technologies&lt;/a&gt;, a product division of Jabil, and follows successful pilots that improved in-store efficiencies and safety.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Jan 2019 04:23:08 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5950</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Oppy urges retailers to “PepperUP” with big Divemex displays</title>
	<description>&lt;span style=&quot;color: #333333;font-family: &#39;Arial&#39;,sans-serif;font-size: 11pt&quot;&gt;COMPANY PRESS RELEASE -- &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;color: black;font-family: &#39;Arial&#39;,sans-serif;font-size: 11pt&quot;&gt;Creative pepper displays can earn cash in more ways than one.&#160; Not only are Sweet Bell peppers the second most popular vegetable behind potatoes, the leading greenhouse vegetable producer Oppy—and grower-partner Divemex—are sponsoring a display contest worth thousands of dollars in prizes early in the new year.&lt;/span&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>14 Jan 2019 04:16:40 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5948</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Limoneira Company announces a record year with 2018 results</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;COMPANY FINANCIAL RELEASE&lt;/strong&gt; --&#160;Limoneira Company, a diversified citrus growing, packing, selling, and marketing company with related agribusiness activities and real estate development operations, reported financial results for the fourth quarter and full fiscal year ended October 31, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Jan 2019 03:16:26 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5985</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Working capital: The lifeblood of a business</title>
	<description>Working capital is very important to the financial health of a business that purchases product and is allowed to pay for that product over time.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Jan 2019 10:51:22 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5944</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Meet the Cabo Diablo</title>
	<description>Company Press Release -- Jacobs Farm Del Cabo, a leader in organic and sustainable farming of fresh herbs and vegetables out of the Central Coast of California and Mexico, has introduced Cabo Diablo Hot Pepper Medley from its Del Cabo brand.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Jan 2019 06:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5935</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA cites Farmers Best of NYC, Inc., for PACA Violations</title>
	<description>&lt;span style=&quot;color: #333333;font-family: &#39;Georgia&#39;,serif&quot;&gt;USDA/AMS RELEASE – &lt;/span&gt;The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) has cited Farmers Best of NYC Inc., operating out of Brooklyn, NY, for failure to pay for produce.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Jan 2019 04:43:01 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5940</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Reducing food waste in fresh produce</title>
	<description>I recently had the pleasure of joining the Produce for Kids Healthy Families Project podcast series.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Jan 2019 03:44:05 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5930</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Landec changes name of food business from Apio to Curation Foods</title>
	<description>&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COMPANY RELEASE&lt;/strong&gt; -- Landec Corporation, a diversified health and wellness company, announced today that it is changing the name of its food business from Apio, Inc.,&#160;to Curation Foods, Inc.,&#160;to signify the completion of its strategic transition from a fresh packaged vegetable company to a branded, natural foods company.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>11 Jan 2019 03:01:36 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5980</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Super Bowl avocado supplies look solid so far</title>
	<description>With less than a month before the No.1 avocado consumption day of the year, a fuel shortage in Mexico could limit supplies.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Jan 2019 01:33:40 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5921</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>How to avoid Avocado Hand</title>
	<description>I learned how to avoid avocado hand from the masters of avocados – Jan DeLyser and Marji Morrow of the California Avocado Commission.</description>
	<pubDate>10 Jan 2019 10:00:59 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5909</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Produce Reporter Week in Review: January 11, 2019</title>
	<description>Greg Johnson, Director of Media Development, and Pamela Riemenschneider, Retail Editor, for Blue Book Services recap this week&#39;s news.</description>
	<pubDate>10 Jan 2019 07:21:41 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5906</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Retailers find SNAP snags during government shutdown</title>
	<description>While feeding programs are being funded during the government shutdown, some retailers are unable to acquire or renew their SNAP licenses, which they say hurts consumers and local economies.</description>
	<pubDate>10 Jan 2019 05:34:59 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5901</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>CDC declares E. coli outbreak over, continues romaine investigation</title>
	<description>The CDC issued a final update on the outbreak of E. coli O157:H7 linked to romaine lettuce grown in California, adding an additional three cases since the last update in mid-December.</description>
	<pubDate>10 Jan 2019 03:52:48 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5897</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Rainier Fruit wraps cause marketing program with holiday donations</title>
	<description>Company Press Release --&#160;The holiday season was a little brighter for some folks in the Yakima area thanks to the efforts of Rainier Fruit.&#160; As part of their Pears for Pairs national marketing campaign benefiting homeless charities, the staff at Rainier Fruit pitched in to make a difference not just nationally, but also at home, raising over $1300 during a holiday dessert auction and coming together to donate hundreds of pairs of socks and towels to the Union Gospel Mission in Yakima, WA.</description>
	<pubDate>10 Jan 2019 03:37:04 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5892</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Topco announces two executive appointments</title>
	<description>COMPANY PRESS RELEASE -- Topco Associates, LLC announced the appointment of two executives, &lt;strong&gt;David Negron&lt;/strong&gt;, Vice President, Meat, Seafood, Deli &amp;amp; Bakery, and &lt;strong&gt;Clint Johnson,&lt;/strong&gt; Vice President, Center Store Operations.</description>
	<pubDate>10 Jan 2019 03:36:44 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5890</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Viva Fresh expands Innovation Awards</title>
	<description>Company Press Release -- The Viva Fresh Expo is taking a new approach for the second annual Gateway to Innovation Awards by expanding its submissions to all types of innovations from the fast-growing, Tex-Mex corridor.</description>
	<pubDate>09 Jan 2019 05:45:36 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5884</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Frieda&#39;s promotes Lunar New Year</title>
	<description>Company Press Release – With February fast approaching, the holiday traditionally celebrated as Chinese New Year is upon us. This year, Frieda’s is innovating to recognize it as Lunar New Year to be more inclusive of all Asian cultures that celebrate the holiday. This is a great opportunity to bring into your store shoppers who are familiar with or curious about Asian cuisine, while appealing to shoppers of all Asian descents. The Year of the Pig will begin on February 5 and be celebrated through February 19.</description>
	<pubDate>09 Jan 2019 05:20:39 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5879</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Who is responsible when produce is frozen in transport?</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;The Problem:&lt;/strong&gt;&#160;Carrier denies full responsibility despite evidence product&#160;was frozen in transit.</description>
	<pubDate>09 Jan 2019 04:47:46 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5870</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Bill Warmerdam, fruit grower-packer of Hanford, CA, dies at 80</title>
	<description>COMPANY PRESS RELEASE -- William (Bill) Warmerdam, a fruit grower-packer-shipper who founded Warmerdam Packing in Hanford, Calif., in 1965 with his wife, Audrey, died on January 8.</description>
	<pubDate>09 Jan 2019 04:44:27 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5864</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>See the new H-E-B Go</title>
	<description>ROUND ROCK, TX—My friends have been raving about the new H-E-B Go for a couple of months now, so I knew I had to check it out.</description>
	<pubDate>09 Jan 2019 04:30:15 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5862</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>MAP: Sprouts adds three states, nine stores to 2019 plans</title>
	<description>Phoenix-based Sprouts Farmers Market released the locations of its second quarter openings, expecting to open 30 stores total in 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>09 Jan 2019 04:20:14 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5857</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Final update on the outbreak of E. coli infections linked to romaine lettuce</title>
	<description>&lt;div class=&quot;card border-0 mb-3&quot;&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>09 Jan 2019 03:25:42 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5887</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Jacobs Farm Del Cabo enhances strategic growth with new sourcing manager</title>
	<description>Company Press Release– Jacobs Farm Del Cabo, a leader in organic and sustainable farming of fresh herbs and vegetables out of the Central Coast of California and Mexico, has hired David Arana as its Strategic Sourcing Manager.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Jan 2019 05:02:26 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5838</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Oppy highlights Pacific Rose apples</title>
	<description>Company Press Release -- Packing a large majority of the Pacific Rose apples grown in the U.S., Crane Family Orchards is especially proud of this season’s crop which is shipping now.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Jan 2019 04:47:10 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5834</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Oppy highlights Pacific Rose apples</title>
	<description>Company Press Release -- Packing a large majority of the Pacific Rose apples grown in the U.S., Crane Family Orchards is especially proud of this season’s crop which is shipping now.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Jan 2019 04:47:10 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5834</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>New bill reignites Florida vs. Mexico tensions</title>
	<description>The Florida vs. Mexico agriculture dispute is heating up again, as three Florida Congressmen have introduced a bill to protect farmers from competition.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Jan 2019 03:29:06 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5830</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Strawberry prices look strong for Valentine’s Day</title>
	<description>Buyers should expect to have strawberries for Valentine’s Day promotions, but supplies won’t be high enough to offer consumers great deals.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Jan 2019 12:19:23 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5825</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Digital 2019 Know Your Commodity Guide Is Available!</title>
	<description>The 2019 digital edition of the&#160;&lt;em&gt;Know Your Commodity Guide&lt;/em&gt;&#160;is here!&#160; This guide provides you with in-depth profile information on an expanded list of commodities, to assist in determining when and from where to source product, good arrival guidelines, and much more.&#160; An additional spotlight on “How consumer trends are shaping produce sales” is also included.</description>
	<pubDate>08 Jan 2019 07:40:57 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5798</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Millennial, Hispanic shoppers outpace organic spending</title>
	<description>In its year-end analysis of Fast Moving Consumer Goods, Chicago-based Nielsen says Americans are spending more on organics than ever before.</description>
	<pubDate>07 Jan 2019 04:56:35 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5805</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Who cares if dollar stores sell more food than Whole Foods?</title>
	<description>&amp;nbsp;</description>
	<pubDate>07 Jan 2019 03:59:54 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5800</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Wegmans starts hiring for first NYC store</title>
	<description>Rochester, NY-based Wegmans Food Markets isn’t planning to open its first New York City location until this fall, but hiring has already begun for select positions.</description>
	<pubDate>07 Jan 2019 02:13:52 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5795</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Landec Corporation reports second quarter 2019 results</title>
	<description>COMPANY FINANCIAL RELEASE --&#160;Landec Corporation (NASDAQ: LNDC), a leading innovator of diversified health and wellness solutions with two operating businesses, Landec Natural Foods (LNF) and Lifecore Biomedical, Inc. reported results for the fiscal 2019 second quarter and first six months ended November 25, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>07 Jan 2019 10:27:06 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5820</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The 2019 Trading &amp;amp; Transportation Guidelines digital edition is available!</title>
	<description>Produce professionals can reference essential updated trading and transportation guidelines, expanded to include a new &lt;em&gt;Select References&lt;/em&gt; section, discussing the Sanitary Transportation Rule, late claims against carriers and much more. &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.bluebookservices.com/BBOS/LearningCenter/TTGuide/2019/index.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; rel=&quot;noopener&quot;&gt;Click here to read the digital edition.&lt;/a&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>07 Jan 2019 07:45:58 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5753</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>MAP: Stop and Shop&#39;s new Long Island footprint</title>
	<description>&lt;p align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Company News Release—Stop &amp;amp; Shop, Quincy, MA, announced today it has agreed to acquire King Kullen Grocery Co., Inc. The agreement includes King Kullen’s 32 supermarkets, five Wild by Nature stores and the use of its corporate office located in Bethpage, N.Y.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>04 Jan 2019 03:47:11 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5772</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Before and After: See Target’s new look in the produce department</title>
	<description>Minneapolis-based Target Corp. is on a mission to remodel 1,000 stores by 2020, and planned to finish remodels of 300 of them in 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Jan 2019 11:48:03 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5755</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Lamb Weston reports second quarter 2019 results</title>
	<description>COMPANY FINANCIAL RELEASE -- Lamb Weston Holdings, Inc., announced&#160;its fiscal second quarter 2019 results and updated its full year outlook.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Jan 2019 10:10:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5817</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The January 2019 Produce Blueprints is here!</title>
	<description>Find out what 2019 produce industry predictions are being made for the perishables supply chain, as well as advice on a range of industry-specific and general business topics with insights from industry professionals.</description>
	<pubDate>04 Jan 2019 01:55:20 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5736</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The local produce paradox</title>
	<description>Consumers love the idea of local produce – and it is certainly amazing when it’s available. But, like many things, the romance often doesn’t live up to life’s realities.</description>
	<pubDate>03 Jan 2019 03:02:28 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5733</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Act Now To Ensure Up-To-Date Listing Information</title>
	<description>The April 2019 Blue Book Deadline approaches.</description>
	<pubDate>03 Jan 2019 10:55:33 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5688</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Fresh produce, the New Year’s diet star</title>
	<description>Each year Americans make New Year’s resolutions, and “eat healthier” or “diet” usually tops this list.</description>
	<pubDate>03 Jan 2019 10:38:22 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5685</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>2018 may have been the worst food safety year</title>
	<description>Just how bad was 2018 for food safety?</description>
	<pubDate>03 Jan 2019 05:00:28 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5661</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Del Monte-backed meal kit company launches 5-minute breakfast and lunch</title>
	<description>Company Press Release: Purple Carrot, the first and only 100% plant-based meal kit company, is announcing&#160;&lt;i&gt;Extras&lt;/i&gt;, a new line of breakfast and lunch offerings to help subscribers eat more plants throughout the day. Just in time for the New Year, these meals have been created to make it even easier for customers looking to incorporate more plant-centric meals into their daily diet, beyond Purple Carrot’s weekly dinner plans.</description>
	<pubDate>02 Jan 2019 04:57:43 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5680</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Del Monte-backed meal kit company launches 5-minute breakfast and lunch</title>
	<description>Company Press Release: Purple Carrot, the first and only 100% plant-based meal kit company, is announcing&#160;&lt;i&gt;Extras&lt;/i&gt;, a new line of breakfast and lunch offerings to help subscribers eat more plants throughout the day. Just in time for the New Year, these meals have been created to make it even easier for customers looking to incorporate more plant-centric meals into their daily diet, beyond Purple Carrot’s weekly dinner plans.</description>
	<pubDate>02 Jan 2019 04:57:43 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5680</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Amazon launches Whole Foods offensive</title>
	<description>The past 18 months have been the quiet before the storm. The grocery world was shaken when Seattle-based Amazon bought Austin, TX-based Whole Foods Market Inc.</description>
	<pubDate>02 Jan 2019 04:36:50 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5675</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SpartanNash announces new Chief Information Officer</title>
	<description>COMPANY PRESS RELEASE -- SpartanNash&#160;announced that Arif Dar will become the new Chief Information Officer (CIO) for the company, effective January 2, 2019. Since 2015, Dar has served as the Chief Information Officer for Racine, Wisconsin-based SC Johnson and Sons, a privately held global manufacturer of household cleaning supplies and consumer goods with operations in more than 60 countries.</description>
	<pubDate>02 Jan 2019 11:13:52 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5749</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>SpartanNash completes acquisition of Indiana-based Martin&#39;s Super Markets</title>
	<description>COMPANY PRESS RELEASE -- SpartanNash announced&#160;that it has completed the previously announced acquisition of Martin&#39;s Super Markets, Inc., a leading family-owned and operated Midwest independent supermarket chain. The transaction closed on December 31, 2018, which is the first day of SpartanNash&#39;s first fiscal quarter of 2019. Under the terms of the agreement, SpartanNash acquired 21 Martin&#39;s Super Markets, eight Fuel Centers, 17 in-store pharmacies, a pharmacy at Saint Joseph Health System in Mishawaka (IN), a Martin&#39;s Express convenience store in South Bend (IN) and a Side Door Caf&#233; at Elkhart General Hospital. SpartanNash will provide additional guidance to the investor community in its fourth quarter 2018 earnings announcement to be released February 19, 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>02 Jan 2019 11:08:46 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5746</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The Produce Reporter daily newsletter</title>
	<description>Happy New Year.</description>
	<pubDate>02 Jan 2019 05:00:17 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5656</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>The produce industry must learn from the 2018 outbreaks</title>
	<description>Many people will remember 2018 as a year of dealing with crushing food safety problems.</description>
	<pubDate>01 Jan 2019 08:00:05 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5658</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Food Trends 2019: Fresh produce to watch</title>
	<description>I’ve already fresh produce items I think will continue to rise in popularity in 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Dec 2018 12:38:42 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5653</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Food Trends 2019: The Low-Hanging…fruit</title>
	<description>I spend a couple of months at the end of every year poring over all the trend predictions for the coming year. Some of them are so niche that I can’t imagine them taking over in a meaningful way in our produce departments.</description>
	<pubDate>28 Dec 2018 12:27:49 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5646</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>VIDEO: Smaller U.S. apple crop has the right mix for consumers</title>
	<description>While the overall apple holdings are down in latest holdings report from the U.S. Apple Association, the increase in Honeycrisp promotions is a perfect fit.</description>
	<pubDate>27 Dec 2018 08:30:24 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5575</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Canadian E. coli outbreak in romaine lettuce appears to be over</title>
	<description>&lt;div&gt;</description>
	<pubDate>24 Dec 2018 11:17:54 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5642</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Best wishes from Blue Book Services</title>
	<description>Everyone at Blue Book wishes you a heartfelt Holiday and Happy New Year.</description>
	<pubDate>24 Dec 2018 01:00:19 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5556</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Raley’s elevates executive to new leadership role</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Company Press Release:&lt;/strong&gt; Raley’s announced the elevation of Deirdre Zimmermann to Chief Customer Experience Officer. Zimmermann has served in an executive position since joining the organization in 2015, beginning as Senior Vice President, Marketing and E-Commerce. Zimmermann will continue to report to Keith Knopf, Raley’s President &amp;amp; Chief Executive Officer.</description>
	<pubDate>20 Dec 2018 03:13:16 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5542</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Brighter Bites in action</title>
	<description>AUSTIN, TX—I stopped by a local elementary school to pack bags for the most recent Brighter Bites distribution to see for myself how the program works.</description>
	<pubDate>20 Dec 2018 11:42:22 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5538</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Calavo Growers, Inc. announces 2018 fourth quarter and full-year results</title>
	<description>&lt;span style=&quot;color: #333333;font-family: &#39;Georgia&#39;,serif&quot;&gt;FINANCIAL RELEASE – &lt;/span&gt;Calavo Growers, Inc.&#160;reported fiscal 2018 fourth quarter and full-year operating results. The company, a global avocado-industry leader and expanding provider of value-added fresh food, said that fiscal 2018 revenues and adjusted net income reached new record highs.</description>
	<pubDate>20 Dec 2018 11:19:45 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5591</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Pepper prices to remain high until new year</title>
	<description>Bell pepper prices have been high for a while, and they aren’t likely to come down until a week or two into 2019.</description>
	<pubDate>19 Dec 2018 04:51:29 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5533</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Wegmans issues voluntary recall</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Company Press Release:&lt;/strong&gt;&#160;Wegmans Food Markets, Inc. has issued a voluntary recall of fresh Cauliflower Rice, Veggie Cauliflower Rice Blend and Stir-Fry Mix with Cauliflower, &lt;b&gt;sold in the produce department between 12/7/18 and 12/18/18,&lt;/b&gt; because it may be contaminated with Escherichia coli O157:H7 bacteria (E. Coli O157:H7). E. coli O157:H7 causes a diarrheal illness often with bloody stools. Although most healthy adults can recover completely within a week, some people can develop a form of kidney failure called Hemolytic Uremic Syndrome (HUS). HUS is most likely to occur in young children and the elderly. The condition can lead to serious kidney damage and even death.</description>
	<pubDate>19 Dec 2018 10:59:21 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5520</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Broccoli, President Bush and the spirit of giving</title>
	<description>HOUSTON—I’m sure many of us in the fresh produce industry are familiar with President George H.W. Bush’s infamous comments about one of our own prized treasures: broccoli.</description>
	<pubDate>19 Dec 2018 09:36:08 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5513</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Gift of Produce resumes after Hurricane Harvey hiatus</title>
	<description>HOUSTON—Hurricane Harvey devastated many areas of Houston, and put a strain on resources – including the Gift of Produce from the Houston Fresh Fruit and Vegetable Association.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Dec 2018 05:16:02 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5508</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Kroger reports third quarter 2018 results</title>
	<description>FINANCIAL RELEASE -- The Kroger Co. reported third quarter 2018 financial results, which ended on November 10, with GAAP net earnings of $317 million, or $0.39 per diluted share. Kroger&#39;s third quarter adjusted operating net earnings were $394 million, or $0.48 per diluted share. &#160;The 2018 third quarter adjustment item relates to the change in the market value of Kroger&#39;s investment in Ocado securities. GAAP net earnings for the third quarter 2017 were $397 million, or $0.44 per diluted share. Kroger reported identical sales growth, without fuel, of 1.6% for the third quarter of 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Dec 2018 02:45:41 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5550</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Costco maintains solid footing</title>
	<description>Costco’s most recently quarterly report got a mixed review from Wall Street analysts and investors, but the warehouse retailer is in very good shape.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Dec 2018 01:30:53 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5482</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Spring Policy Summit to feature USMCA/NAFTA negotiator Salvador Behar</title>
	<description>Company Press Release: The Fresh Produce Association of the Americas will be hosting the Spring Policy Summit March 19-20, 2019, at the Tubac Golf Resort and Spa in Tubac, Arizona. The FPAA is excited to present several new speakers this year.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Dec 2018 11:21:33 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5479</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Kroger announces succession plan for Chief Financial Officer, J. Michael Schlotman</title>
	<description>Company Press Release: The Kroger Co. announced its succession plan for Chief Financial Officer.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Dec 2018 09:44:05 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5477</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>FDA investigating outbreak of E. coli infections likely linked to romaine lettuce</title>
	<description>FDA Recall: The FDA, along with CDC, state and local agencies, is investigating a multistate outbreak of &lt;i&gt;E. coli&lt;/i&gt; O157:H7 illnesses linked to romaine lettuce grown in California this fall. The Public Health Agency of Canada (PHAC) and Canadian Food Inspection Agency (CFIA) are also coordinating with U.S. agencies as they investigate a similar outbreak in Canada.</description>
	<pubDate>18 Dec 2018 07:45:03 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5471</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Business changes faster than you think</title>
	<description>If you think financial conditions cannot change in a hurry, think again. General Electric is a great example of a former financial behemoth that is now struggling to survive.</description>
	<pubDate>17 Dec 2018 11:54:54 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5449</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Spokane Produce voluntarily recalls product</title>
	<description>COMPANY PRESS RELEASE / PRODUCE RECALL - Spokane Produce Inc. of Spokane, WA initiates a &lt;strong&gt;voluntary recall of sandwiches containing green leaf lettuce and foodservice lettuce filets&lt;/strong&gt; following notice of a produce industry ingredient recall by Adam Bros. Farming Inc. Sandwich products bearing the &lt;strong&gt;Northwest Cuisine Creations and Fresh &amp;amp; Local labels&lt;/strong&gt;. These products are recalled because they may be contaminated with Escherichia coli O157:H7 bacteria (E. Coli O157:H7). E. coli O157:H7 causes a diarrheal illness often with bloody stools. Although most healthy adults can recover completely within a week, some people can develop a form of kidney failure called Hemolytic Uremic Syndrome (HUS). HUS is most likely to occur in young children and the elderly. The condition can lead to serious kidney damage and even death.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Dec 2018 04:17:32 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5463</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Apio, Inc., voluntarily recalls selected Salad Shake Ups™</title>
	<description>COMPANY PRESS RELEASE&#160;/ PRODUCT RECALL -- Apio, Inc. of Guadalupe, California is voluntarily recalling five SKUs of Eat Smart&lt;sup&gt;&#174;&lt;/sup&gt; Single-Serve Salad Shake Ups&lt;sup&gt;™&lt;/sup&gt; (bowls). The recall comes after the Canadian Food Inspection Agency (CFIA) informed the company that one random sample of Eat Smart Single-Serve Salad Shake Ups Sweet Kale/Chou Frise Doux 156 gr. (5.5oz) with Best Before of Dec 14, 2018 tested positive for Listeria Monocytogenes. As a precautionary measure, Apio is&#160;recalling all products produced on the same day, same production line, as the one sample that tested positive by CFIA. At this time, they are not aware of any illnesses linked by health officials to this recall and no other products are affected by this recall.</description>
	<pubDate>15 Dec 2018 03:49:38 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5454</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Reflections on New York Produce Show</title>
	<description>NEW YORK – The New York Produce Show reinforced to attendees how global the fresh produce industry has become.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Dec 2018 04:17:20 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5442</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Chelan Fruit Cooperative announces new interim CEO</title>
	<description>COMPANY PRESS RELEASE -- Chelan Fruit Cooperative board of directors announced that chief executive officer Reggie Collins will transition from his current position to an advisory position effective Jan. 1, 2019. He will also work with Chelan Fresh Marketing on business and strategic opportunities.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Dec 2018 04:09:49 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5458</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Ron Carkoski announces retirement</title>
	<description>&lt;strong&gt;Company Press Release:&lt;/strong&gt; Ron Carkoski, who has served as the CEO of four Seasons Family of Companies since 2002, will be retiring on Dec 21st, 2018. Ron started his career at Four Seasons Produce in 1994 as the Director of Procurement after previous leadership roles at Gateway Foods in Wisconsin.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Dec 2018 03:15:54 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5434</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>HKW announces acquisition of Fresh Direct Produce</title>
	<description>Company Press Release: Hammond, Kennedy, Whitney &amp;amp; Company, Inc. (&quot;HKW&quot;), a private equity firm focused on partnering with talented management teams to build world-class companies, announces the acquisition of Fresh Direct Produce, LLC (&quot;Fresh Direct Produce&quot;). Fresh Direct Produce is a distributor of fresh, ethnic, tropical, organic, and specialty produce.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Dec 2018 02:01:55 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5421</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>FDA names farm, narrows scope of romaine outbreak</title>
	<description>The Food and Drug Administration named Adam Bros. Farming of Santa Maria, CA, as testing positive for the E. coli strain involved in the romaine outbreak.</description>
	<pubDate>14 Dec 2018 10:44:25 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5412</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Report: Whole Foods, Instacart to part ways</title>
	<description>Shortly after Instacart lowered its fees nationwide – making Whole Foods deliveries via Amazon Prime Now costlier – the Wall Street Journal is reporting Whole Foods and Instacart are calling it quits.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Dec 2018 02:24:55 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5403</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Costco Wholesale Corporation reports first quarter 2019 results</title>
	<description>&lt;span style=&quot;color: #333333;font-family: &#39;Georgia&#39;,serif&quot;&gt;FINANCIAL RELEASE – &lt;/span&gt;Costco Wholesale Corporation&#160;announced its operating results for the first quarter (twelve weeks) of fiscal 2019, ended November 25, 2018.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Dec 2018 11:01:12 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5584</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Produce for Better Health Foundation to Inspire Influencers and Share New Ways to Promote Fruit and Vegetables at The New York Produce Show and Conference</title>
	<description>BRENTWOOD, Mo. (December 13, 2018) – The Produce for Better Health Foundation (PBH) and Produce Business were co-presenters at the Connect with Fresh Media Program — an invite-only lunch workshop for more than 50 influential writers, registered dietitians, lifestyle bloggers, and food and culinary experts, held during the New York Produce Show and Conference at the Javits Center in New York City on Dec. 12.</description>
	<pubDate>13 Dec 2018 08:00:07 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5243</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Produce industry sees many victories in farm bill</title>
	<description>After months of debate, both the House of Representatives and the Senate passed the farm bill rather quickly this week, and fresh produce was one of the winners.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Dec 2018 05:11:15 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5353</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Del Monte Foods announces limited recall of canned &quot;fiesta corn&quot; with peppers</title>
	<description>COMPANY PRODUCT RECALL -- Del Monte Foods Inc. announced a recall of 64,242 cases of FIESTA CORN Seasoned with Red &amp;amp; Green Peppers due to under processing. These deviations were part of the commercial sterilization process and could result in contamination by spoilage organisms or pathogens, which could lead to life-threatening illness if consumed. &lt;strong&gt;It is important to note that there have been no reports of illness associated with these products to date&lt;/strong&gt;. No other production codes or products are affected by this recall.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Dec 2018 10:43:24 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5394</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Dalton Thomas announced as 2019 &quot;Apple Citizen of the Year&quot;</title>
	<description>COMPANY PRESS RELEASE -- Dalton Thomas has been named 2019 Apple Citizen of the Year. Festival Administrator Darci Christoferson and Former Wenatchee Valley College Athletic Director, Sandy Cooprider surprised Dalton with the award at the Oneonta Starr Ranch Growers Christmas Party at the Wenatchee Golf and Country Club, Friday evening. The Apple Citizen of the Year award began in 1981 to honor the roots of the fruit industry and the leaders that make this the Wenatchee Valley the Apple Capital of the World.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Dec 2018 10:25:11 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5391</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Produce stays above political fray</title>
	<description>Fruits and vegetables aren’t affected in the&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fns.usda.gov/school-meals/fr-121218&quot;&gt; latest school meals rule&lt;/a&gt; and will remain an important part of the program.</description>
	<pubDate>12 Dec 2018 09:02:58 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5331</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Food Trends 2019: The Has-beens</title>
	<description>In November and December of every year, food industry “observers” and so-called experts come up with a seemingly random list of foods consumers are all going to be excited about over the next 12 months.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Dec 2018 03:31:42 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5326</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>United Fresh encourages quick passage of Farm Bill – this week</title>
	<description>Company Press Release – The United Fresh Produce Association applauds the House and the Senate Farm Bill Conference Committee for approving a Farm Bill conference report, the final report to H.R. 2, the Agriculture Improvement Act of 2018. This legislation will direct policy and funding resources for key agriculture programs in the Federal Government for the next five years.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Dec 2018 01:29:44 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5322</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>Food bloggers weigh in on trend realities</title>
	<description>Company Press Release —&#160; For the second year in a row FullTilt Marketing, Orlando, FL, surveyed food bloggers from across the country to get their perspective on what they view as the relevant food trends and how those trends are shaping meal time realities for every day consumers.</description>
	<pubDate>11 Dec 2018 01:23:55 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5317</guid>
</item>
<item>
	<title>USDA cites Tumi Produce International Corp. for PACA Violations</title>
	<description>&lt;span style=&quot;color: #333333;font-family: &#39;Georgia&#39;,serif&quot;&gt;USDA/AMS PRESS RELEASE – &lt;/span&gt;The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA) has cited Tumi Produce International Corp., Bronx, N.Y., for failure to pay for produce.</description>
	<pubDate>10 Dec 2018 02:29:04 -0500</pubDate>
	<author></author>
	<guid>http://azqa.apps.bluebookservices.com/bbos/NewsArticleView.aspx?ArticleID=5277</guid>
</item>

	</channel>
</rss>
